# id fc76cef4-3a91-4394-b6d4-be7c4ed840d5	domain=train
his _ _ O
playlist _ _ O
includes _ _ O
sonny _ _ B-PER
sharrock _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
gza _ _ B-PER
, _ _ O
country _ _ B-GRP
teasers _ _ I-GRP
and _ _ O
the _ _ B-PER
notorious _ _ I-PER
b.i.g. _ _ I-PER

# id f1f78d1e-1d16-41fd-a9b3-52559949b11c	domain=train
all _ _ O
songs _ _ O
written _ _ O
by _ _ O
m.o.d. _ _ B-GRP
, _ _ O
unless _ _ O
otherwise _ _ O
stated _ _ O

# id aacf70c5-dec4-4b8f-836e-ba2c4607de39	domain=train
he _ _ O
worked _ _ O
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
bookstore _ _ B-GRP
before _ _ O
becoming _ _ O
a _ _ O
journalist _ _ O
, _ _ O
first _ _ O
for _ _ O
le _ _ B-GRP
devoir _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
then _ _ O
for _ _ O
cité _ _ B-CW
libre _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
for _ _ O
which _ _ O
he _ _ O
later _ _ O
became _ _ O
the _ _ O
director _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5806a9e5-0c0a-4850-8148-c3151359b2f9	domain=train
rinder _ _ O
did _ _ O
not _ _ O
speak _ _ O
on _ _ O
camera _ _ O
because _ _ O
he _ _ O
promised _ _ O
his _ _ O
first _ _ O
interview _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
bbc _ _ B-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 37495040-c9c9-437f-aa23-90ad96b89d8f	domain=train
indigenous _ _ O
outlaw _ _ O
musquito _ _ B-PER
defied _ _ O
colonial _ _ O
law _ _ O
and _ _ O
led _ _ O
attacks _ _ O
on _ _ O
settlers _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id a52dd345-0ad8-40a7-88a5-5053fc80a23d	domain=train
a _ _ O
code _ _ B-CW
generation _ _ I-CW
usually _ _ O
converts _ _ O
some _ _ O
intermediate _ _ O
representation _ _ O
of _ _ O
source _ _ O
code _ _ O
into _ _ O
machine _ _ O
code _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id a97f0d75-57e7-4a16-b956-d70525bbc2c5	domain=train
the _ _ O
main _ _ O
contractor _ _ O
was _ _ O
ssangyong _ _ B-CORP
engineering _ _ I-CORP
and _ _ I-CORP
construction _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id f6d6a381-5ed0-423c-8076-63659fbea283	domain=train
in _ _ O
2010 _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
musical _ _ O
instrument _ _ O
maestro _ _ O
raghav _ _ B-PER
sachar _ _ I-PER
was _ _ O
the _ _ O
highlight _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
event _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id bf8790c4-3cf9-4c17-82f0-1e02a1f8b0c3	domain=train
she _ _ O
became _ _ O
opposed _ _ O
to _ _ O
abortion _ _ O
in _ _ O
1992 _ _ O
while _ _ O
attending _ _ O
a _ _ O
bible _ _ B-CW
study _ _ O
and _ _ O
has _ _ O
since _ _ O
spoken _ _ O
out _ _ O
about _ _ O
how _ _ O
abortion _ _ O
has _ _ O
negatively _ _ O
impacted _ _ O
her _ _ O
life _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f118c528-430f-4063-b621-f36ad56c217e	domain=train
france _ _ O
proletarian _ _ B-GRP
unity _ _ I-GRP
party _ _ I-GRP
( _ _ O
pup _ _ O
) _ _ O
( _ _ O
from _ _ O
1933 _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id 494a05a9-0fa5-414f-b57c-8c455677cfc7	domain=train
for _ _ O
example _ _ O
, _ _ O
in _ _ O
one _ _ O
advertisement _ _ O
a _ _ O
woman _ _ O
wearing _ _ O
a _ _ O
yellow _ _ O
shirt _ _ O
and _ _ O
a _ _ O
pin _ _ O
is _ _ O
juxtaposed _ _ O
with _ _ O
a _ _ O
similarly _ _ O
colored _ _ O
piece _ _ O
of _ _ O
pie _ _ B-PROD
. _ _ O

# id 130ab99c-65d5-40a0-b996-5187c9b0c7ab	domain=train
the _ _ B-GRP
guardian _ _ I-GRP
described _ _ O
the _ _ O
album _ _ O
's _ _ O
release _ _ O
as _ _ O
one _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
50 _ _ O
key _ _ O
events _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
history _ _ O
of _ _ O
r&b _ _ O
and _ _ O
hip _ _ O
hop _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 2e684f84-58a3-456c-8c07-fe600866d25c	domain=train
the _ _ O
crew _ _ O
intended _ _ O
the _ _ O
movie _ _ O
to _ _ O
be _ _ O
a _ _ O
continuation _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
season _ _ O
five _ _ O
finale _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
end _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
was _ _ O
also _ _ O
meant _ _ O
to _ _ O
stand _ _ O
on _ _ O
its _ _ O
own _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 40edbb1f-d9c3-46d3-ba13-c649a737083d	domain=train
the _ _ O
gameplay _ _ O
has _ _ O
been _ _ O
described _ _ O
as _ _ O
action _ _ O
heavy _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
compared _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
ratchet _ _ B-CW
& _ _ I-CW
clank _ _ I-CW
series _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 396f521a-fd9c-4b74-94e4-11e327af1c2e	domain=train
mingus _ _ O
left _ _ O
in _ _ O
1951 _ _ O
and _ _ O
red _ _ B-PER
mitchell _ _ I-PER
replaced _ _ O
him _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 4bf88485-0239-48b5-ae9e-ab27d89dd3b9	domain=train
american _ _ O
weekly _ _ O
radio _ _ O
show _ _ O
wait _ _ B-CW
wait... _ _ I-CW
don't _ _ I-CW
tell _ _ I-CW
me! _ _ I-CW
was _ _ O
started _ _ O
in _ _ O
1998 _ _ O
on _ _ O
public _ _ O
radio _ _ O
network _ _ O
npr _ _ B-CORP
. _ _ O

# id cc713d03-fe96-438f-8f66-25dd45c6cfa8	domain=train
hanna _ _ O
died _ _ O
in _ _ O
st. _ _ B-LOC
george _ _ I-LOC
in _ _ O
2019 _ _ O
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
age _ _ O
of _ _ O
90 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 005a6790-233d-4c5f-95d0-5292957bba8f	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
developed _ _ O
by _ _ O
a _ _ O
team _ _ O
led _ _ O
by _ _ O
former _ _ O
blizzard _ _ B-CORP
entertainment _ _ I-CORP
employees _ _ O
, _ _ O
some _ _ O
of _ _ O
whom _ _ O
had _ _ O
overseen _ _ O
the _ _ O
creation _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
diablo _ _ B-CW
series _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 92a66f8a-7365-4631-a745-f8e8e054a034	domain=train
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
winter _ _ O
months _ _ O
, _ _ O
snowmobile _ _ B-PROD
is _ _ O
also _ _ O
popular _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id cb42a990-f48d-489d-a734-d36e97b1cc6d	domain=train
black _ _ B-CW
swan _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
co _ _ O
production _ _ O
with _ _ O
cross _ _ B-GRP
creek _ _ I-GRP
pictures _ _ I-GRP
and _ _ O
phoenix _ _ B-GRP
pictures _ _ I-GRP
) _ _ O

# id 895ab3ff-2bb9-43e0-a85e-4679cb40e399	domain=train
the _ _ O
play _ _ O
interweaves _ _ O
the _ _ O
lives _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
poet _ _ O
w. _ _ B-PER
h. _ _ I-PER
auden _ _ I-PER
and _ _ O
the _ _ O
mathematician _ _ O
alan _ _ B-PER
turing _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 59e19ca3-ebc9-4762-b71c-6d25c92e03f8	domain=train
the _ _ O
1988 _ _ O
elections _ _ O
were _ _ O
also _ _ O
held _ _ O
on _ _ O
a _ _ O
non _ _ O
party _ _ O
basis _ _ O
, _ _ O
although _ _ O
around _ _ O
30 _ _ O
candidates _ _ O
sympathetic _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
muslim _ _ B-GRP
brotherhood _ _ I-GRP
were _ _ O
elected _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id dbb3e457-74dd-4add-8068-f98145aa7ee8	domain=train
she _ _ O
fronted _ _ O
the _ _ O
band _ _ O
gossip _ _ B-GRP
from _ _ O
its _ _ O
formation _ _ O
in _ _ O
1999 _ _ O
until _ _ O
its _ _ O
dissolution _ _ O
in _ _ O
2016 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 386ec660-9bf0-4784-b2f8-8d076b9fae0c	domain=train
a _ _ O
european _ _ B-GRP
union _ _ I-GRP
directive _ _ O
which _ _ O
covers _ _ O
high _ _ O
visibility _ _ O
clothing _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 242b4300-1709-467d-9343-8ae6174aff4b	domain=train
the _ _ O
game _ _ O
uses _ _ O
a _ _ O
battery _ _ O
packed _ _ O
random-access _ _ B-PROD
memory _ _ I-PROD
in _ _ O
order _ _ O
to _ _ O
save _ _ O
progress _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 097c3dbe-09ff-4dd0-93dd-60f6aafe94d0	domain=train
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
end _ _ O
the _ _ O
best _ _ O
placed _ _ O
rider _ _ O
was _ _ O
wilfried _ _ B-PER
cretskens _ _ I-PER
who _ _ O
finished _ _ O
61st _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e78bcb79-52ad-4938-b75c-d19d4dfce4e8	domain=train
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
429 _ _ O
delegates _ _ O
who _ _ O
attended _ _ O
, _ _ O
over _ _ O
one _ _ O
third _ _ O
were _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ O
area _ _ O
around _ _ O
wheeling _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 7ad6b87a-80aa-478f-9d98-2e914707cccd	domain=train
in _ _ O
doing _ _ O
so _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
reunited _ _ O
with _ _ O
former _ _ O
high _ _ O
school _ _ O
and _ _ O
college _ _ O
teammate _ _ O
malik _ _ B-PER
jackson _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 58d12e07-bb65-45bd-9511-0f6da66aca37	domain=train
modelled _ _ O
for _ _ O
yves _ _ B-PER
saint _ _ I-PER
laurent _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
versace _ _ B-CORP
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
karl _ _ B-PER
lagerfeld _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 09defc13-be3a-44b8-9f74-f071d618c867	domain=train
# _ _ O
after _ _ O
exercising _ _ O
and _ _ O
a _ _ O
shower _ _ O
, _ _ O
birdman _ _ B-CW
. _ _ O

# id fd6767db-12e0-4748-b469-f66c6ccb9557	domain=train
there _ _ O
remained _ _ O
the _ _ O
question _ _ O
of _ _ O
whether _ _ O
the _ _ O
improved _ _ O
performance _ _ O
compared _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
automated _ _ O
kh-8 _ _ B-PROD
gambit _ _ I-PROD
3 _ _ I-PROD
satellite _ _ O
then _ _ O
under _ _ O
development _ _ O
justified _ _ O
the _ _ O
cost _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id d9a0350b-2d3f-4302-a760-376c045e7dea	domain=train
the _ _ O
group _ _ O
smith _ _ B-GRP
recorded _ _ O
a _ _ O
version _ _ O
on _ _ O
their _ _ O
1969 _ _ O
debut _ _ O
album _ _ O
, _ _ O
sung _ _ O
by _ _ O
gayle _ _ B-PER
mccormick _ _ I-PER

# id f6285e99-68b2-49cf-a821-16756d558195	domain=train
bamboo _ _ O
, _ _ O
like _ _ O
wood _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
natural _ _ O
composite _ _ B-PROD
material _ _ I-PROD
with _ _ O
a _ _ O
high _ _ O
strength _ _ O
to _ _ O
weight _ _ O
ratio _ _ O
useful _ _ O
for _ _ O
structures _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 1dd73a26-35ee-4260-8bcc-f7874f077ae1	domain=train
in _ _ O
previous _ _ O
years _ _ O
he _ _ O
had _ _ O
worked _ _ O
with _ _ O
alex _ _ B-PER
cox _ _ I-PER
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
soundtracks _ _ O
of _ _ O
his _ _ O
films _ _ O
sid _ _ B-CW
and _ _ I-CW
nancy _ _ I-CW
and _ _ O
walker _ _ B-CW
in _ _ O
1986 _ _ O
and _ _ O
1987 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 7e4138f8-3391-4bf6-81ac-b0e5c5feab89	domain=train
historian _ _ O
françois _ _ B-PER
furet _ _ I-PER
was _ _ O
originally _ _ O
slated _ _ O
to _ _ O
write _ _ O
the _ _ O
introduction _ _ O
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
he _ _ O
died _ _ O
before _ _ O
being _ _ O
able _ _ O
to _ _ O
do _ _ O
so _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 289173e8-83d0-4d83-a4f8-3ba00d642ed1	domain=train
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
main _ _ O
hub _ _ O
of _ _ O
fiji _ _ B-CORP
airways _ _ I-CORP
and _ _ O
its _ _ O
domestic _ _ O
and _ _ O
regional _ _ O
subsidiary _ _ O
fiji _ _ B-CORP
link _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 46806e1d-aea8-421b-b371-9cebdc62d8dd	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
broadcast _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
channel _ _ O
animal _ _ B-CORP
planet _ _ I-CORP
, _ _ O
with _ _ O
episodes _ _ O
having _ _ O
aired _ _ O
between _ _ O
2001 _ _ O
and _ _ O
2003 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5af1184f-774f-4de4-bd2c-2af3e45ed174	domain=train
it _ _ O
stars _ _ O
jeetendra _ _ B-PER
, _ _ O
moushumi _ _ B-PER
chatterjee _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
govinda _ _ B-PER
, _ _ O
shilpa _ _ B-PER
shirodkar _ _ I-PER
with _ _ O
music _ _ O
composed _ _ O
by _ _ O
rajesh _ _ B-PER
roshan _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id fc807a98-9e22-4327-be34-6f7d043272a7	domain=train
variety _ _ O
suggested _ _ O
that _ _ O
the _ _ O
mid _ _ O
may _ _ O
opening _ _ O
date _ _ O
was _ _ O
overshadowed _ _ O
by _ _ O
the _ _ O
socko _ _ O
b.o. _ _ O
of _ _ O
ip _ _ B-CW
man _ _ I-CW
2 _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id 93e529ae-fb68-4712-acec-500ed2cd7f72	domain=train
he _ _ O
picked _ _ O
up _ _ O
his _ _ O
dad _ _ O
’s _ _ O
banjo _ _ O
at _ _ O
age _ _ O
8 _ _ O
and _ _ O
by _ _ O
the _ _ O
time _ _ O
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
11 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
had _ _ O
a _ _ O
gibson _ _ B-CORP
banjo _ _ O
endorsement _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 202758e3-79b7-4725-bbea-d7a455291c85	domain=train
a _ _ O
term _ _ O
loan _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
monetary _ _ O
loan _ _ B-PROD
that _ _ O
is _ _ O
repaid _ _ O
in _ _ O
regular _ _ O
payments _ _ O
over _ _ O
a _ _ O
set _ _ O
period _ _ O
of _ _ O
time _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f1b548cf-c005-43a1-b1eb-596204d5d19b	domain=train
then _ _ O
he _ _ O
became _ _ O
a _ _ O
salesman _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
later _ _ O
a _ _ O
public _ _ B-PROD
relations _ _ I-PROD
consultant _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id dcfe2620-dbc6-41e5-9f9b-7f12455a9eec	domain=train
riccardo _ _ B-PER
ghedin _ _ I-PER
/ _ _ O
stéphane _ _ B-PER
robert _ _ I-PER
def _ _ O
. _ _ O
arnaud _ _ B-PER
clément _ _ I-PER
/ _ _ O
olivier _ _ B-PER
rochus _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
6 _ _ O
– _ _ O
2 _ _ O
, _ _ O
5 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
, _ _ O
[ _ _ O
10 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
] _ _ O

# id c09807db-853f-4789-8006-57b268a1bca6	domain=train
many _ _ O
buildings _ _ O
were _ _ O
built _ _ O
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
brick _ _ O
nonplastering _ _ O
style _ _ O
characterized _ _ O
by _ _ O
a _ _ O
special _ _ O
kind _ _ O
of _ _ O
decorative _ _ B-CW
arts _ _ I-CW
using _ _ O
colored _ _ O
, _ _ O
figured _ _ O
bricks _ _ O
, _ _ O
usually _ _ O
yellow _ _ O
and _ _ O
red _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id aa268db3-5cb9-4d00-816d-ff380b19a80f	domain=train
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
juku _ _ B-CORP
in _ _ O
tokyo _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
established _ _ O
over _ _ O
300 _ _ O
years _ _ O
ago _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 41eedba2-d3e4-4d43-9cbb-0ad9c72a52b0	domain=train
the _ _ O
city _ _ O
is _ _ O
also _ _ O
home _ _ O
to _ _ O
via _ _ B-GRP
university _ _ I-GRP
college _ _ I-GRP
which _ _ O
brings _ _ O
a _ _ O
lot _ _ O
of _ _ O
international _ _ O
students _ _ O
to _ _ O
move _ _ O
to _ _ O
this _ _ O
town _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id b4e603bc-d944-48c8-bef8-5506a3e65a25	domain=train
fleur _ _ O
live _ _ O
stenogram _ _ O
and _ _ O
recording _ _ O
at _ _ O
echo _ _ B-CORP
of _ _ I-CORP
moscow _ _ I-CORP
( _ _ O
rus _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id 14689355-ed37-44ff-8df2-d802cb7b9834	domain=train
refrigerator _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
device _ _ O
used _ _ O
to _ _ O
cool _ _ O
objects _ _ O
or _ _ O
interior _ _ O
spaces _ _ O

# id a7c3eea1-8687-4cc8-9c97-f1f23cb36c1a	domain=train
in _ _ O
1920 _ _ O
, _ _ O
she _ _ O
accompanied _ _ O
her _ _ O
father _ _ O
to _ _ O
rio _ _ B-LOC
de _ _ I-LOC
janeiro _ _ I-LOC
and _ _ O
são _ _ B-LOC
paulo _ _ I-LOC
, _ _ O
where _ _ O
she _ _ O
was _ _ O
well _ _ O
received _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9610b08c-b105-492f-876b-794b15a1e15a	domain=train
vanadzor _ _ O
( _ _ O
) _ _ O
is _ _ O
an _ _ O
urban _ _ O
municipal _ _ O
community _ _ O
and _ _ O
the _ _ O
third _ _ O
largest _ _ O
city _ _ O
in _ _ O
armenia _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
serving _ _ O
as _ _ O
the _ _ O
capital _ _ O
of _ _ O
lori _ _ B-LOC
region _ _ I-LOC
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
northern _ _ O
part _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
country _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e8724c98-328e-40b6-bc8e-cc0b09c720da	domain=train
lauren _ _ B-PER
jackson _ _ I-PER
has _ _ O
won _ _ O
the _ _ O
award _ _ O
four _ _ O
times _ _ O
, _ _ O
while _ _ O
kelsey _ _ B-PER
griffin _ _ I-PER
has _ _ O
won _ _ O
the _ _ O
award _ _ O
three _ _ O
times _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id abe88e39-d835-4f9b-b25a-5a9c50ee5a79	domain=train
401 _ _ O
designates _ _ O
a _ _ O
373 _ _ O
cc _ _ O
engine _ _ O
, _ _ O
derived _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ O
ktm _ _ B-PROD
390 _ _ I-PROD
duke _ _ I-PROD
of _ _ O
street _ _ O
bikes _ _ O

# id 2a0ea54c-e5f2-4595-b499-e823fecc2778	domain=train
oakland _ _ O
's _ _ O
defense _ _ O
, _ _ O
anchored _ _ O
by _ _ O
defensive _ _ O
end _ _ O
john _ _ B-PER
matuszak _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
was _ _ O
punishing _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e03f618a-03de-456d-a795-2a72e8a8601e	domain=train
recipes _ _ O
vary _ _ O
slightly _ _ O
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
the _ _ O
dish _ _ O
is _ _ O
basically _ _ O
crème _ _ B-PROD
caramel _ _ I-PROD
made _ _ O
out _ _ O
of _ _ O
eggs _ _ O
and _ _ O
sweetened _ _ O
milk _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 7119f8c3-f585-4138-b28c-f1dda07bb154	domain=train
# _ _ O
i _ _ B-CW
fought _ _ I-CW
the _ _ I-CW
law _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
sonny _ _ B-PER
curtis _ _ I-PER
) _ _ O
− _ _ O
2 _ _ O
: _ _ O
35 _ _ O
( _ _ O
the _ _ B-GRP
crickets _ _ I-GRP
cover _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id c8e2d38c-77ef-4067-8554-c94881bbf135	domain=train
however _ _ O
she _ _ O
has _ _ O
to _ _ O
settle _ _ O
for _ _ O
silver _ _ O
medal _ _ O
after _ _ O
she _ _ O
lost _ _ O
to _ _ O
akane _ _ B-PER
yamaguchi _ _ I-PER
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
tightly _ _ O
contested _ _ O
final _ _ O
match _ _ O
of _ _ O
3 _ _ O
games _ _ O
21 _ _ O
– _ _ O
14 _ _ O
, _ _ O
18 _ _ O
– _ _ O
21 _ _ O
, _ _ O
13 _ _ O
– _ _ O
21 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 11df49ff-22ec-440a-bdcb-feeae2796635	domain=train
david _ _ B-PER
foster _ _ I-PER
wallace _ _ I-PER
2011 _ _ O
novel _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
pale _ _ I-CW
king _ _ I-CW
alludes _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
poem _ _ O
in _ _ O
its _ _ O
title _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 39de9d51-b754-47a2-bf71-a0fdbfad95b3	domain=train
one _ _ O
maglite _ _ B-CORP
of _ _ O
rechargeable _ _ O
focusing _ _ O
flashlight _ _ O
uses _ _ O
a _ _ O
halogen _ _ O
lamp _ _ O
and _ _ O
produces _ _ O
218 _ _ O
lumens _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id aa19875b-ef2e-482d-adb6-4d8a9d73a81b	domain=train
afs _ _ B-GRP
intercultural _ _ I-GRP
programs _ _ I-GRP
international _ _ O
youth _ _ O
exchange _ _ O
program _ _ O
, _ _ O
founded _ _ O
in _ _ O
1915 _ _ O

# id 31474e3e-744e-48de-8ee4-ab4c51fa3c05	domain=train
the _ _ O
natural _ _ O
and _ _ O
architectural _ _ O
ensemble _ _ O
of _ _ O
stolac _ _ B-LOC

# id 44ecedb1-d6f3-4801-8b89-b7a82aacfc31	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
also _ _ O
used _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
netflix _ _ B-CORP
series _ _ O
stranger _ _ B-CW
things _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id b1a4bf9e-3040-4909-8220-5b144b94ad0b	domain=train
she _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
card _ _ O
carrying _ _ O
geek _ _ B-PROD
and _ _ O
considers _ _ O
herself _ _ O
boy _ _ O
proof _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
proud _ _ O
of _ _ O
it _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9df84a6a-fbf8-4443-b4f5-68988c7a2298	domain=train
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
tactical _ _ B-CW
role-playing _ _ I-CW
game _ _ I-CW
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
playstation _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
developed _ _ O
and _ _ O
published _ _ O
by _ _ O
namco _ _ B-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 53471bc1-7bd0-4a5f-8042-c50eb1c76c77	domain=train
he _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
co _ _ O
founder _ _ O
and _ _ O
president _ _ O
of _ _ O
greentown _ _ B-CORP
china _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 2d4c03e6-2008-48da-bd5b-ac8a0e7f11d5	domain=train
he _ _ O
played _ _ O
4 _ _ O
games _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
united _ _ B-CORP
rugby _ _ I-CORP
championship _ _ I-CORP
club _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id a8a188e1-680d-4ca3-92db-3efd222b1096	domain=train
the _ _ O
philosopher _ _ O
and _ _ O
historian _ _ O
, _ _ O
władysław _ _ B-PER
tatarkiewicz _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
was _ _ O
his _ _ O
grandson _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f853ae21-b018-4382-a767-816ba07f9bd6	domain=train
duo _ _ O
, _ _ O
with _ _ O
michael _ _ B-PER
wollny _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
piano _ _ O
) _ _ O
; _ _ O
in _ _ O
concert _ _ O

# id 3833c877-f888-4713-a4c3-40057bf284b8	domain=train
jane _ _ B-PER
fonda _ _ I-PER
– _ _ O
julia _ _ B-CW
as _ _ O
lillian _ _ B-PER
hellman _ _ I-PER

# id 9a908eb8-962c-4248-a3dd-1720b4666968	domain=train
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
first _ _ O
episode _ _ O
of _ _ O
season _ _ O
thirty _ _ O
one _ _ O
of _ _ O
jeopardy! _ _ B-CW
, _ _ O
jeopardy _ _ O
! _ _ O

# id b5f465e7-a854-4dce-a027-dac0606e83c9	domain=train
the _ _ O
pair _ _ O
also _ _ O
run _ _ O
a _ _ O
separate _ _ O
podcasting _ _ B-CW
channel _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ea916f1b-b9a5-4959-9537-aeb875c1faf1	domain=train
his _ _ O
work _ _ O
is _ _ O
held _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
collections _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
j. _ _ B-LOC
paul _ _ I-LOC
getty _ _ I-LOC
museum _ _ I-LOC
, _ _ O
metropolitan _ _ B-LOC
museum _ _ I-LOC
of _ _ I-LOC
art _ _ I-LOC
, _ _ O
museum _ _ B-LOC
of _ _ I-LOC
fine _ _ I-LOC
arts, _ _ I-LOC
houston _ _ I-LOC
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
museum _ _ B-LOC
of _ _ I-LOC
modern _ _ I-LOC
art _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 8d7d50df-015d-43a7-ac46-8c1e9dfe465a	domain=train
he _ _ O
taught _ _ O
this _ _ O
line _ _ O
of _ _ O
work _ _ O
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
accademia _ _ B-GRP
albertina _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 5e1a950e-5a79-4603-868c-956730134f00	domain=train
after _ _ O
a _ _ O
long _ _ O
break _ _ O
, _ _ O
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
beginning _ _ O
of _ _ O
1996 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
issued _ _ O
naposletku... _ _ B-CW
( _ _ O
after _ _ O
all _ _ O
. _ _ O
. _ _ O
. _ _ O
) _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 2e92f2f2-fbed-4642-8029-b29c2669253e	domain=train
she _ _ O
also _ _ O
meets _ _ O
two _ _ O
versions _ _ O
of _ _ O
jesus _ _ B-PER
— _ _ O
a _ _ O
kindly _ _ O
but _ _ O
ineffective _ _ O
young _ _ O
man _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
another _ _ O
who _ _ O
makes _ _ O
a _ _ O
living _ _ O
by _ _ O
posing _ _ O
for _ _ O
an _ _ O
artist _ _ O
depicting _ _ O
him _ _ O
on _ _ O
a _ _ O
cross _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 0862314b-1f83-42b4-8e09-078469e89a2c	domain=train
bbc _ _ B-CORP
radio _ _ I-CORP
3 _ _ I-CORP
has _ _ O
also _ _ O
played _ _ O
their _ _ O
music _ _ O
in _ _ O
mainstream _ _ O
programmes _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 1d45d106-21e0-4da7-b53f-390cd644964d	domain=train
the _ _ O
first _ _ O
type _ _ O
was _ _ O
built _ _ O
by _ _ O
hohenzollern _ _ B-CORP
locomotive _ _ I-CORP
works _ _ I-CORP
and _ _ O
baldwin _ _ B-CORP
locomotive _ _ I-CORP
works _ _ I-CORP
in _ _ O
1928 _ _ O
and _ _ O
1929 _ _ O
respectively _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 938a2a9b-0c8f-4b84-b4ed-e77ac56b8bb6	domain=train
due _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
fact _ _ O
that _ _ O
there _ _ O
are _ _ O
two _ _ O
different _ _ O
materials _ _ O
in _ _ O
dfsw _ _ O
; _ _ O
formation _ _ O
of _ _ O
a _ _ O
composite _ _ B-PROD
material _ _ I-PROD
structure _ _ O
within _ _ O
the _ _ O
nugget _ _ O
zone _ _ O
is _ _ O
inevitable _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ff5c5359-9ebf-445a-a4de-2e8d3abf85fb	domain=train
the _ _ O
club _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
member _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
galway _ _ B-GRP
gaa _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 6cf512c6-8383-497f-8e6f-cb5563052883	domain=train
one _ _ O
of _ _ O
his _ _ O
doctoral _ _ O
students _ _ O
was _ _ O
kazimierz _ _ B-PER
twardowski _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 1a875457-a8f3-41e3-ba17-5609e52425e2	domain=train
after _ _ O
the _ _ O
association _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
two _ _ O
newspapers _ _ O
, _ _ O
léon _ _ B-PER
nicole _ _ I-PER
served _ _ O
as _ _ O
their _ _ O
editor _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 0c13c99c-0ebc-48cd-a218-6014bd013c1f	domain=train
danses _ _ O
concertantes _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
work _ _ O
for _ _ O
chamber _ _ O
orchestra _ _ O
by _ _ O
igor _ _ B-PER
stravinsky _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
composed _ _ O
in _ _ O
1942 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ef030a2a-93f9-4e09-8aed-e20d67d45bef	domain=train
jeanne _ _ B-PER
marni _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
1854 _ _ O
– _ _ O
1910 _ _ O
, _ _ O
france _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O
nv _ _ O
. _ _ O
& _ _ O
pw _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id d8e7dbc2-6002-452d-8a9e-ec17d6e6d955	domain=train
the _ _ O
vendor _ _ O
members _ _ O
sell _ _ O
street _ _ B-PROD
food _ _ I-PROD
or _ _ O
other _ _ O
goods _ _ O
, _ _ O
such _ _ O
as _ _ O
fresh _ _ O
flowers _ _ O
and _ _ O
toys _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 65fc8c67-3b31-4dee-b488-fb9c508111a3	domain=train
he _ _ O
played _ _ O
in _ _ O
major _ _ B-CORP
league _ _ I-CORP
baseball _ _ I-CORP
( _ _ O
mlb _ _ O
) _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
baltimore _ _ B-GRP
orioles _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id cc14d714-ac17-4166-900d-501972fa4406	domain=train
welenchiti _ _ O
is _ _ O
served _ _ O
by _ _ O
a _ _ O
railway _ _ O
station _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
addis _ _ B-LOC
ababa–djibouti _ _ I-LOC
railway _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 24130875-9e1b-4747-bba4-bd0e465e6739	domain=train
among _ _ O
these _ _ O
peoples _ _ O
turquoise _ _ O
was _ _ O
used _ _ O
in _ _ O
mosaic _ _ B-PROD
inlay _ _ O
, _ _ O
in _ _ O
sculptural _ _ O
works _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
was _ _ O
fashioned _ _ O
into _ _ O
toroidal _ _ O
beads _ _ O
and _ _ O
freeform _ _ O
pendants _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f60c4d0b-a721-422e-89ee-3fdfad20a69d	domain=train
in _ _ O
1990 _ _ O
italian _ _ B-CORP
post _ _ I-CORP
issued _ _ O
a _ _ O
stamp _ _ O
in _ _ O
his _ _ O
honor _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 850fb7b1-b5b3-4d12-875e-50ac6021de68	domain=train
approximately _ _ O
2,169 _ _ O
developers _ _ O
across _ _ O
14 _ _ O
studios _ _ O
worked _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
last _ _ I-CW
of _ _ I-CW
us _ _ I-CW
part _ _ I-CW
ii _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id 537d918b-82bd-4bf7-8a3e-fcc15eeaf5dc	domain=train
in _ _ O
1613 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
continued _ _ O
his _ _ O
education _ _ O
at _ _ O
university _ _ B-GRP
of _ _ I-GRP
basel _ _ I-GRP
( _ _ O
where _ _ O
his _ _ O
grandfather _ _ O
had _ _ O
also _ _ O
studied _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O
in _ _ O
geneva _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
sedan _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 2ab5e20b-f215-4df9-943c-fc3fa218761e	domain=train
the _ _ O
music _ _ O
video _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
title _ _ O
track _ _ O
was _ _ O
filmed _ _ O
by _ _ O
canon _ _ B-CORP
inc. _ _ I-CORP
as _ _ O
a _ _ O
campaign _ _ O
for _ _ O
their _ _ O
4k _ _ O
canon _ _ B-PROD
eos _ _ I-PROD
c500 _ _ I-PROD
camera _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5ce3e012-ebc8-43cd-9767-3fca146fd9e4	domain=train
in _ _ O
2017 _ _ O
, _ _ O
amy _ _ B-PER
chu _ _ I-PER
began _ _ O
writing _ _ O
the _ _ O
series _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5c5f989a-1d79-4110-824f-b06250a5cb38	domain=train
guinness _ _ B-CW
world _ _ I-CW
records _ _ I-CW
2002 _ _ O
classified _ _ O
it _ _ O
as _ _ O
the _ _ O
most _ _ O
valuable _ _ O
tooth _ _ O
, _ _ O
which _ _ O
would _ _ O
value _ _ O
approximately _ _ O
£ _ _ O
25,000 _ _ O
( _ _ O
35,700 _ _ O
) _ _ O
in _ _ O
late _ _ O
2001 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 34b0d123-d739-4e1f-aa98-be2a50e3b7f0	domain=train
the _ _ O
show _ _ O
makes _ _ O
extensive _ _ O
use _ _ O
of _ _ O
1980s _ _ O
popular _ _ O
music _ _ O
, _ _ O
including _ _ O
nena _ _ B-PER
99 _ _ B-CW
luftballons _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
david _ _ B-PER
bowie _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
new _ _ B-GRP
order _ _ I-GRP
and _ _ O
eurythmics _ _ B-GRP
among _ _ O
others _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9d75d49d-33dc-4cb4-823b-1650448b33cf	domain=train
it _ _ O
fixed _ _ O
some _ _ O
bugs _ _ O
and _ _ O
added _ _ O
support _ _ O
for _ _ O
half _ _ O
height _ _ O
floppy _ _ O
drives _ _ O
and _ _ O
the _ _ O
new _ _ O
ibm _ _ B-PROD
pcjr _ _ I-PROD
. _ _ O

# id 87695bf4-c9c0-49cb-89f5-826361e47fb3	domain=train
the _ _ O
following _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
list _ _ O
of _ _ O
works _ _ O
about _ _ O
paris _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
france _ _ B-LOC
: _ _ O

# id 3267ff5d-d846-4bea-9267-ee1f123f6374	domain=train
parry _ _ O
thomas _ _ O
became _ _ O
chief _ _ O
engineer _ _ O
at _ _ O
leyland _ _ B-CORP
motors _ _ I-CORP
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
company _ _ O
whose _ _ O
main _ _ O
products _ _ O
were _ _ O
commercial _ _ O
vehicles _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ab968c63-faf3-462a-9a74-f89e2a284e45	domain=train
mongolia _ _ O
has _ _ O
an _ _ O
embassy _ _ O
in _ _ O
tokyo _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
established _ _ O
in _ _ O
1973 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 4fd01ea5-2158-42be-a86b-e233bd9056f5	domain=train
comprising _ _ O
several _ _ O
municipalities _ _ O
and _ _ O
urban _ _ O
centres _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
subregion _ _ O
's _ _ O
capital _ _ O
is _ _ O
setúbal _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
includes _ _ O
several _ _ O
cities _ _ O
including _ _ O
almada _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
setúbal _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 2a5bb14a-0e73-4c23-94e9-e62738457f73	domain=train
in _ _ O
1923 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
founded _ _ O
the _ _ O
organization _ _ O
rodobrana _ _ B-GRP
( _ _ O
home _ _ O
guard _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O
an _ _ O
armed _ _ O
militia _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 6153a171-b13b-43a5-a084-41fc9cf6cb41	domain=train
she _ _ O
began _ _ O
working _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
series _ _ O
as _ _ O
a _ _ O
producer _ _ O
and _ _ O
screenwriter _ _ O
in _ _ O
2007 _ _ O
during _ _ O
the _ _ O
series _ _ O
desperate _ _ B-CW
housewives, _ _ I-CW
season _ _ I-CW
4 _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id 0b124490-8bc5-49d9-a375-7c945df621a8	domain=train
these _ _ O
online _ _ O
features _ _ O
were _ _ O
still _ _ O
considered _ _ O
a _ _ O
breakthrough _ _ O
in _ _ O
video _ _ O
games _ _ O
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
the _ _ O
competing _ _ O
playstation _ _ B-PROD
2 _ _ I-PROD
did _ _ O
not _ _ O
ship _ _ O
with _ _ O
a _ _ O
built _ _ O
in _ _ O
network _ _ O
adapter _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 10c7c3f4-ddc6-4ecf-a647-9dc63786ae01	domain=train
built _ _ O
in _ _ O
germany _ _ B-LOC
by _ _ O
h. _ _ B-CORP
c. _ _ I-CORP
stülcken _ _ I-CORP
sohn _ _ I-CORP
at _ _ O
steinwerder _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
hamburg _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id f4deffa4-234b-407c-83d3-497826365849	domain=train
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
a _ _ O
versatile _ _ O
actor _ _ O
who _ _ O
could _ _ O
handle _ _ O
with _ _ O
ease _ _ O
the _ _ O
hand _ _ B-PROD
fan _ _ I-PROD
used _ _ O
by _ _ O
poor _ _ O
scholars _ _ O
and _ _ O
pheasant _ _ O
plumes _ _ O
worn _ _ O
by _ _ O
generals _ _ O
on _ _ O
their _ _ O
helmets _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f062f7a2-3ecd-4bb5-a809-3ed4bbcad802	domain=train
porkins _ _ O
has _ _ O
gained _ _ O
some _ _ O
comedic _ _ O
notoriety _ _ O
due _ _ O
to _ _ O
his _ _ O
size _ _ O
, _ _ O
manner _ _ O
and _ _ O
untimely _ _ O
death _ _ O
, _ _ O
which _ _ O
was _ _ O
spoofed _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
family _ _ B-CW
guy _ _ I-CW
episode _ _ O
blue _ _ B-CW
harvest _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id 0c5b827e-6d25-49af-bfa5-bac2b018e4e1	domain=train
during _ _ O
his _ _ O
childhood _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
accompanied _ _ O
his _ _ O
father _ _ O
to _ _ O
meetings _ _ O
of _ _ O
alcoholics _ _ B-GRP
anonymous _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 2e8d14a6-b106-4c62-8ae1-87b189de3d9b	domain=train
eulenhald _ _ O
near _ _ O
waldleiningen _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
( _ _ O
c _ _ O
. _ _ O
19 _ _ O
ha _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O

# id 27a7c297-3ca8-472a-ada1-0116af0e3c7c	domain=train
when _ _ O
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
freed _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
rushed _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
court _ _ O
of _ _ O
charles _ _ B-PER
v _ _ I-PER
of _ _ I-PER
france _ _ I-PER
to _ _ O
renew _ _ O
his _ _ O
allegiance _ _ O
and _ _ O
rejoin _ _ O
bertrand _ _ B-PER
du _ _ I-PER
guesclin _ _ I-PER
troops _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 36da1701-a5a7-4cbe-a707-5674221dcb5b	domain=train
he _ _ O
later _ _ O
trained _ _ O
under _ _ O
then _ _ O
consejo _ _ B-GRP
mundial _ _ I-GRP
de _ _ I-GRP
lucha _ _ I-GRP
libre _ _ I-GRP
lead _ _ O
trainer _ _ O
el _ _ B-PER
satánico _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 09c67087-59a0-4a5b-8920-00ff43851d0d	domain=train
character _ _ O
has _ _ O
an _ _ O
unlockable _ _ O
alternate _ _ O
livery _ _ B-PROD
. _ _ O

# id 0f5ed288-100d-4469-ae67-d3b96d6b8967	domain=train
runners _ _ O
up _ _ O
: _ _ O
chocolat _ _ B-CW
• _ _ O
france _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
camille _ _ B-CW
claudel _ _ I-CW
• _ _ O
france _ _ B-LOC

# id 8f2f886d-8122-4d34-b218-3addd496fd0c	domain=train
it _ _ O
's _ _ O
also _ _ O
seen _ _ O
in _ _ O
toy _ _ B-CW
story _ _ I-CW
2 _ _ I-CW
and _ _ O
a _ _ O
trailer _ _ O
for _ _ O
toy _ _ B-CW
story _ _ I-CW
3 _ _ I-CW

# id 73047169-cd55-4d66-ba03-9960767fe0df	domain=train
his _ _ O
son _ _ O
, _ _ O
shintarō _ _ B-PER
hirase _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
( _ _ O
1884 _ _ O
1939 _ _ O
) _ _ O
was _ _ O
also _ _ O
a _ _ O
malacologist _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id fd8a723e-5244-40de-bcc7-dc916a40f283	domain=train
malcolm _ _ B-PER
todd _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
73 _ _ O
, _ _ O
historian _ _ O
and _ _ O
archaeologist _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id fc90e731-ede3-43b3-b30c-e414503ff9ff	domain=train
liu _ _ B-PER
wanting _ _ I-PER
sun _ _ B-PER
shengnan _ _ I-PER
6 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
( _ _ O
1 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O
6 _ _ O
– _ _ O
3 _ _ O
, _ _ O
[ _ _ O
10 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
] _ _ O

# id e8f69c2a-17ea-495a-ab66-a0d5d550fb0f	domain=train
during _ _ O
a _ _ O
1981 _ _ O
annual _ _ O
review _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
uncovered _ _ O
a _ _ O
$ _ _ O
50 _ _ O
million _ _ O
fraud _ _ O
scheme _ _ O
involving _ _ O
ad _ _ O
powerhouse _ _ O
j. _ _ B-CORP
walter _ _ I-CORP
thompson _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 6da2102d-41d0-402d-b71c-e63a2ad4318b	domain=train
while _ _ O
auditioning _ _ O
for _ _ O
television _ _ O
and _ _ O
film _ _ O
roles _ _ O
, _ _ O
she _ _ O
worked _ _ O
on _ _ O
theatre _ _ B-GRP
productions _ _ O
of _ _ O
romeo _ _ B-CW
and _ _ I-CW
juliet _ _ I-CW
and _ _ O
arsenic _ _ B-CW
and _ _ I-CW
old _ _ I-CW
lace _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id 45632026-e303-46cd-a646-5a062e077990	domain=train
eliot _ _ O
graduated _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ O
yale _ _ B-GRP
university _ _ I-GRP
( _ _ O
later _ _ O
known _ _ O
as _ _ O
yale _ _ O
college _ _ O
) _ _ O
in _ _ O
1706 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 07cd4ad0-97c2-45a9-9508-39afd68f6b84	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
the _ _ O
world _ _ O
's _ _ O
first _ _ O
computer _ _ B-PROD
reservations _ _ I-PROD
system _ _ I-PROD
for _ _ O
trains _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 136bc35f-afcd-4072-bd77-21442cb28e38	domain=train
michel _ _ B-PER
sanchez _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
who _ _ O
was _ _ O
member _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
band _ _ O
deep _ _ B-GRP
forest _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
co _ _ O
wrote _ _ O
the _ _ O
lyrics _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 3d463405-50ea-4156-8467-4777acc8ec64	domain=train
his _ _ O
last _ _ O
theatrical _ _ O
composition _ _ O
was _ _ O
music _ _ O
for _ _ O
joan _ _ B-CW
the _ _ I-CW
woman _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
starring _ _ O
geraldine _ _ B-PER
farrar _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id d25433c3-f46a-4b29-9da6-4760bf9f0738	domain=train
the _ _ O
rest _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
beat _ _ O
is _ _ O
constructed _ _ O
out _ _ O
of _ _ O
machine _ _ O
gun _ _ O
sprays _ _ O
, _ _ O
nintendo _ _ B-CORP
themes _ _ O
and _ _ O
bottle _ _ O
blows _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 989ea4e5-3418-48bc-b1b1-59669c0594ff	domain=train
vlade _ _ B-PER
divac _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
basketball _ _ O
player _ _ O
, _ _ O
general _ _ O
manager _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
sacramento _ _ B-GRP
kings _ _ I-GRP

# id a088aec1-9824-4d3c-9a03-be02bed8d1b8	domain=train
he _ _ O
is _ _ O
known _ _ O
for _ _ O
presenting _ _ O
the _ _ O
nos _ _ B-CW
journaal _ _ I-CW
from _ _ O
1996 _ _ O
till _ _ O
2009 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9d0b1490-3ef5-485e-be57-c5063ae99e43	domain=train
she _ _ O
started _ _ O
her _ _ O
career _ _ O
as _ _ O
a _ _ O
consultant _ _ O
with _ _ O
pricewaterhousecoopers _ _ B-CORP
in _ _ O
kenya _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 7d865daf-d18b-4232-90ff-b1a309a4af51	domain=train
bygrave _ _ O
lives _ _ O
in _ _ O
queenscliff _ _ B-LOC
with _ _ O
her _ _ O
husband _ _ O
, _ _ O
multi _ _ O
award _ _ O
winning _ _ O
writer _ _ O
and _ _ O
poet _ _ O
barry _ _ B-PER
hill _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id db34d60a-8bc3-47c3-bbc3-e287889f08e4	domain=train
a _ _ O
new _ _ O
recording _ _ O
of _ _ O
this _ _ O
work _ _ O
was _ _ O
made _ _ O
in _ _ O
1993 _ _ O
with _ _ O
tom _ _ B-PER
waits _ _ I-PER
singing _ _ O
along _ _ O
with _ _ O
the _ _ O
original _ _ O
recording _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
vagrant _ _ O
during _ _ O
the _ _ O
final _ _ O
section _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 961f7f66-8542-4f6c-80be-5b678a447c62	domain=train
it _ _ O
essentially _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
collarless _ _ O
polo _ _ B-PROD
shirt _ _ I-PROD
. _ _ O

# id fdc5cb20-0076-4d0d-acd2-68782f6b1e36	domain=train
pragoti _ _ B-CORP
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
state _ _ O
run _ _ O
automotive _ _ O
industry _ _ O
, _ _ O
which _ _ O
assembles _ _ O
mitsubishi _ _ B-PROD
pajero _ _ I-PROD
sport _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
tata _ _ B-CORP
motors _ _ I-CORP
trucks _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
ashok _ _ B-CORP
leyland _ _ I-CORP
minibus _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9eca1cb0-5714-4f89-ba72-5678d86ad6a9	domain=train
he _ _ O
has _ _ O
previously _ _ O
worked _ _ O
at _ _ O
networks _ _ O
including _ _ O
channel _ _ B-CORP
4 _ _ I-CORP
, _ _ O
itv _ _ B-CORP
and _ _ O
al _ _ B-CORP
jazeera _ _ I-CORP
english _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id f57b0843-e6df-4fa4-87e7-e0d46207f12a	domain=train
july _ _ O
21 _ _ O
– _ _ O
mos _ _ B-CORP
burger _ _ I-CORP
was _ _ O
founded _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id b9799a06-3a97-46f6-99ca-b1ba7ac5a10c	domain=train
mbali _ _ B-PER
ntuli _ _ I-PER
was _ _ O
appointed _ _ O
as _ _ O
his _ _ O
successor _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5959ed1f-db8d-4739-9b11-d5faaaee343f	domain=train
her _ _ O
brother _ _ O
was _ _ O
the _ _ O
conservative _ _ B-GRP
party _ _ I-GRP
politician _ _ O
rab _ _ B-PER
butler _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 81cb2eb4-877d-418b-a3b0-b6c620a04568	domain=train
cross _ _ O
with _ _ O
nail _ _ B-PROD
in _ _ O
evros _ _ B-LOC
regional _ _ I-LOC
unit _ _ I-LOC
/ _ _ O
greece _ _ O
] _ _ O
] _ _ O

# id 1cdcda17-fe18-425f-90b7-e2c54f43c4f1	domain=train
he _ _ O
served _ _ O
as _ _ O
the _ _ O
head _ _ O
football _ _ O
coach _ _ O
at _ _ O
allegheny _ _ B-GRP
college _ _ I-GRP
from _ _ O
2002 _ _ O
to _ _ O
2015 _ _ O
, _ _ O
compiling _ _ O
a _ _ O
record _ _ O
of _ _ O
62 _ _ O
– _ _ O
79 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id cb774320-15fa-4e47-a098-afae86759119	domain=train
røyken _ _ O
videregående _ _ O
skole _ _ O
is _ _ O
an _ _ O
unesco _ _ B-GRP
aspnet _ _ I-GRP
school _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
offers _ _ O
several _ _ O
international _ _ O
exchange _ _ O
programs _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id fcd6b511-ef63-4459-8670-21a9ebd3a144	domain=train
the _ _ O
video _ _ O
was _ _ O
a _ _ O
10 _ _ O
minute _ _ O
long _ _ O
short _ _ B-CW
film _ _ I-CW
and _ _ O
gathered _ _ O
an _ _ O
audience _ _ O
of _ _ O
400 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 3dbc02af-6a4e-4fb7-9017-71c4a848452b	domain=train
the _ _ O
book _ _ O
received _ _ O
praise _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
economist _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
the _ _ B-GRP
guardian _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
bill _ _ B-PER
gates _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
who _ _ O
called _ _ O
it _ _ O
one _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
best _ _ O
books _ _ O
on _ _ O
energy _ _ O
that _ _ O
has _ _ O
been _ _ O
written _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id a59d45ab-71db-4def-a0d8-a7e7873825be	domain=train
she _ _ O
recorded _ _ O
jingles _ _ O
for _ _ O
major _ _ O
companies _ _ O
such _ _ O
as _ _ O
toyota _ _ B-CORP
, _ _ O
american _ _ B-CORP
airlines _ _ I-CORP
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
max _ _ B-CORP
factor _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 6ade758e-0649-4229-8496-4c216bec4cd2	domain=train
the _ _ O
game _ _ O
is _ _ O
based _ _ O
upon _ _ O
the _ _ O
fantasy _ _ O
novels _ _ O
nine _ _ B-CW
princes _ _ I-CW
in _ _ I-CW
amber _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
doubleday _ _ B-CORP
1970 _ _ O
) _ _ O
and _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
guns _ _ I-CW
of _ _ I-CW
avalon _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
doubleday _ _ O
1972 _ _ O
) _ _ O
by _ _ O
roger _ _ B-PER
zelazny _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id fe8c948d-e24a-47f7-a924-4f421959fb08	domain=train
the _ _ O
series _ _ O
also _ _ O
produced _ _ O
spin _ _ O
off _ _ O
titles _ _ O
including _ _ O
saga _ _ B-CW
and _ _ O
mana _ _ B-CW
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
in _ _ O
turn _ _ O
influenced _ _ O
later _ _ O
game _ _ O
developers _ _ O
and _ _ O
studios _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e9ef13bc-ba67-42a4-bb08-68670e8d671b	domain=train
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
hbo _ _ B-CORP
game _ _ B-CW
of _ _ I-CW
thrones _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
is _ _ O
portrayed _ _ O
by _ _ O
charles _ _ B-PER
dance _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 3c455b11-6163-488b-a02b-f6381af61082	domain=train
a _ _ O
popular _ _ O
use _ _ O
is _ _ O
rendering _ _ O
an _ _ O
animated _ _ O
3d _ _ O
scene _ _ O
as _ _ O
an _ _ O
adobe _ _ B-CW
flash _ _ I-CW
file _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id bd3005f5-9e00-42e6-816d-6e1c42885f5c	domain=train
he _ _ O
also _ _ O
opened _ _ O
a _ _ O
studio _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
isle _ _ B-GRP
of _ _ I-GRP
man _ _ I-GRP
where _ _ O
he _ _ O
spent _ _ O
his _ _ O
summers _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 070b6ced-2f6d-48cb-94c5-e54fe8972ba4	domain=train
the _ _ O
album _ _ O
was _ _ O
released _ _ O
in _ _ O
1990 _ _ O
by _ _ O
sparrow _ _ B-CORP
records _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id a1ae6fba-7548-4215-bdd8-7ea9ec96fbd4	domain=train
postman _ _ B-CW
pat _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
1981 _ _ O
, _ _ O
1991 _ _ O
– _ _ O
1994 _ _ O
, _ _ O
1996 _ _ O
, _ _ O
2004 _ _ O
– _ _ O
2008 _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id 86cb2d58-c36f-445f-b0c7-48497e5cfede	domain=train
he _ _ O
stayed _ _ O
in _ _ O
leipzig _ _ B-LOC
in _ _ O
1768 _ _ O
and _ _ O
hamburg _ _ B-LOC
in _ _ O
1769 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 6fcbddb6-19a5-49a0-8821-121c0c9e0591	domain=train
in _ _ O
more _ _ O
recent _ _ O
years _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
has _ _ O
served _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
boards _ _ O
of _ _ O
media _ _ O
companies _ _ O
such _ _ O
as _ _ O
cbs _ _ B-CORP
and _ _ O
chicago _ _ B-GRP
tribune _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 6a7722a5-32c1-49b8-9b14-322c13d5fd28	domain=train
aerogel _ _ O
has _ _ O
the _ _ O
density _ _ O
of _ _ O
glass _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
another _ _ O
silicon _ _ O
based _ _ O
solid _ _ O
to _ _ O
which _ _ O
it _ _ O
may _ _ O
be _ _ O
compared _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 8cddaeb6-8dc1-4a54-8e06-f482d53afa0f	domain=train
the _ _ O
film _ _ O
had _ _ O
musical _ _ O
score _ _ O
by _ _ O
b. _ _ B-PER
a. _ _ I-PER
chidambaranath _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id eef9b527-a91b-4794-b089-e6acaaf91db2	domain=train
her _ _ O
mother _ _ O
was _ _ O
an _ _ O
opera _ _ B-CW
singer _ _ O
and _ _ O
her _ _ O
father _ _ O
worked _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
textile _ _ O
industry _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 6fa84cfb-1750-4649-9950-27ca0981c1a3	domain=train
pinky _ _ O
wore _ _ O
the _ _ O
same _ _ O
outfit _ _ O
as _ _ O
in _ _ O
her _ _ O
happy _ _ B-CW
days _ _ I-CW
episodes _ _ O
, _ _ O
though _ _ O
her _ _ O
hair _ _ O
was _ _ O
now _ _ O
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
70s _ _ O
style _ _ O
shag _ _ O
cut _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ed3608fe-3290-4ca2-8b06-42bab5532f12	domain=train
iron _ _ B-CW
sky _ _ I-CW
and _ _ O
nazis _ _ B-CW
at _ _ I-CW
the _ _ I-CW
center _ _ I-CW
of _ _ I-CW
the _ _ I-CW
earth _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
both _ _ O
released _ _ O
in _ _ O
2012 _ _ O
) _ _ O
are _ _ O
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
similar _ _ O
vein _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id fa1ac13b-553d-43cb-9a71-f74a58f90afa	domain=train
they _ _ O
were _ _ O
extensively _ _ O
refurbished _ _ O
between _ _ O
1989 _ _ O
and _ _ O
1992 _ _ O
by _ _ O
eastleigh _ _ B-CORP
works _ _ I-CORP
, _ _ O
for _ _ O
use _ _ O
on _ _ O
services _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
isle _ _ B-LOC
of _ _ I-LOC
wight _ _ I-LOC
island _ _ B-LOC
line, _ _ I-LOC
isle _ _ I-LOC
of _ _ I-LOC
wight _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 5c8f61b7-d034-450e-bf83-c6d6a2870aaa	domain=train
ac _ _ B-PROD
propulsion _ _ I-PROD
ebox _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
type _ _ O
of _ _ O
automobile _ _ O

# id 68dd3974-888a-4aa9-86d8-9636fed53367	domain=train
a _ _ O
2014 _ _ O
rolling _ _ B-CW
stone _ _ I-CW
reader _ _ O
's _ _ O
poll _ _ O
ranked _ _ O
it _ _ O
the _ _ O
group _ _ O
's _ _ O
fourth _ _ O
best _ _ O
song _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 75981173-f61e-448c-ab32-4508ccd13f33	domain=train
mos _ _ B-PER
def _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
talib _ _ B-PER
kweli _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
that _ _ O
whole _ _ O
rawkus _ _ B-CORP
records _ _ I-CORP
scene _ _ O
, _ _ O
that _ _ O
's _ _ O
my _ _ O
type _ _ O
of _ _ O
shit _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 1e79e60c-4d83-4e86-a520-7fd71bd226f6	domain=train
the _ _ O
philippine _ _ B-GRP
daily _ _ I-GRP
inquirer _ _ I-GRP
is _ _ O
founded _ _ O
and _ _ O
publishes _ _ O
its _ _ O
first _ _ O
issue _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9a083801-8c37-4fd0-804e-98c7cf239d65	domain=train
the _ _ B-CW
hollywood _ _ I-CW
reporter _ _ I-CW
estimated _ _ O
the _ _ O
film _ _ O
lost _ _ O
the _ _ O
studio _ _ O
around _ _ O
$ _ _ O
70 _ _ O
million _ _ O
, _ _ O
when _ _ O
factoring _ _ O
together _ _ O
all _ _ O
expenses _ _ O
and _ _ O
revenues _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id a6bca4ce-bb6b-4098-b859-960ace1675fc	domain=train
the _ _ O
film _ _ O
is _ _ O
available _ _ O
for _ _ O
free _ _ O
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
website _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
national _ _ B-GRP
library _ _ I-GRP
of _ _ I-GRP
norway _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id c0ed3198-8342-49c4-8c7a-be4bef52ead3	domain=train
he _ _ O
conducted _ _ O
two _ _ O
albums _ _ O
, _ _ O
both _ _ O
for _ _ O
decca _ _ B-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 1fdfb9bc-63ee-494e-8c2f-cedb0dca558b	domain=train
tesla _ _ B-CORP
. _ _ O
( _ _ O
defunct _ _ O
; _ _ O
was _ _ O
active _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
1980s _ _ O
and _ _ O
1990s _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id cbb9b5b6-49cd-40d1-b4a7-e3f208e50bda	domain=train
brian _ _ B-PER
j. _ _ I-PER
smith _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
born _ _ O
1981 _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O
actor _ _ O
, _ _ O
stargate _ _ B-CW
universe _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
sense8 _ _ B-CW

# id 3de4e94a-3195-429c-a57d-76f9c11e9b2e	domain=train
during _ _ O
the _ _ O
reign _ _ O
of _ _ O
ibn _ _ B-PER
saud _ _ I-PER
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
the _ _ O
most _ _ O
significant _ _ O
non _ _ O
royal _ _ O
official _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 1b5a26ba-0713-4c2c-8fe5-9c141ebdf789	domain=train
tithes _ _ O
) _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
seventh _ _ O
tractate _ _ O
of _ _ O
zeraim _ _ B-CW
( _ _ O
order _ _ O
of _ _ O
seeds _ _ O
) _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
mishnah _ _ B-CW
, _ _ O
tosefta _ _ B-CW
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
the _ _ O
jerusalem _ _ B-CW
talmud _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id 845494f9-71f0-4102-8ad2-fc1ad1033b68	domain=train
de3 _ _ O
– _ _ O
0-4-0 _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
400 _ _ O
hp _ _ O
, _ _ O
50 _ _ O
tons _ _ O
, _ _ O
25 _ _ O
mph _ _ O

# id 02f5b1e6-8bf3-4be3-937e-d989f8f82c4e	domain=train
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
located _ _ O
north _ _ O
of _ _ O
elgin _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
about _ _ O
south _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
washington _ _ B-LOC
border _ _ O
, _ _ O
at _ _ O
an _ _ O
elevation _ _ O
of _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 0958d6cc-d56d-45c9-99dc-75c80be56f2b	domain=train
the _ _ O
main _ _ O
river _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
district _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
saale _ _ B-LOC
with _ _ O
wine _ _ B-PROD
along _ _ O
the _ _ O
river _ _ O
valley _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 971d32c7-2dc7-4fb1-be3b-dcb4005661f4	domain=train
the _ _ O
western _ _ B-GRP
canada _ _ I-GRP
hockey _ _ I-GRP
league _ _ I-GRP
was _ _ O
the _ _ O
first _ _ O
major _ _ O
professional _ _ O
league _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
prairies _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e646f569-5338-4a88-9cbb-1cf602f7c25e	domain=train
harvey _ _ B-PER
brooks _ _ I-PER
– _ _ O
bass _ _ O
guitar _ _ O
( _ _ O
highway _ _ O
61 _ _ O
revisited _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id 0bc2373e-ee08-492a-8655-2c96814f6235	domain=train
established _ _ O
in _ _ O
1972 _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
pakistan _ _ B-GRP
naval _ _ I-GRP
air _ _ I-GRP
arm _ _ I-GRP
provides _ _ O
fleet _ _ O
air _ _ O
defence _ _ O
, _ _ O
maritime _ _ O
reconnaissance _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
anti _ _ O
submarine _ _ O
warfare _ _ O
capability _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 75c5c94c-af6b-46ee-b128-a62515f74be6	domain=train
one _ _ O
was _ _ O
intercepted _ _ O
by _ _ O
iron _ _ B-PROD
dome _ _ I-PROD
; _ _ O
the _ _ O
other _ _ O
fell _ _ O
in _ _ O
an _ _ O
open _ _ O
area _ _ O
near _ _ O
the _ _ O
city _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id d529ab83-7adf-4f08-ad68-6b98e4815974	domain=train
he _ _ O
also _ _ O
appeared _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
film _ _ O
crossroads _ _ B-CW
. _ _ O

# id 2fbc9514-6819-45a6-9841-6dadf87f9015	domain=train
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
included _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
list _ _ O
of _ _ O
100 _ _ O
most _ _ O
influential _ _ O
indian _ _ O
by _ _ O
the _ _ B-GRP
indian _ _ I-GRP
express _ _ I-GRP
and _ _ O
also _ _ O
named _ _ O
journalist _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
year _ _ O
by _ _ O
mumbai _ _ O
press _ _ O
club _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 110d4745-f762-4e95-b353-fa92c41fba84	domain=train
for _ _ O
example _ _ O
, _ _ O
typical _ _ O
fresh _ _ O
chili _ _ O
peppers _ _ O
have _ _ O
a _ _ O
water _ _ O
content _ _ O
around _ _ O
90 _ _ O
% _ _ O
, _ _ O
whereas _ _ O
tabasco _ _ B-PROD
sauce _ _ I-PROD
has _ _ O
a _ _ O
water _ _ O
content _ _ O
of _ _ O
95 _ _ O
% _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id eb0273dd-2880-497a-80de-b0cfe9865345	domain=train
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
fourth _ _ O
single _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ O
former _ _ O
duo _ _ O
's _ _ O
first _ _ O
extended _ _ B-CW
play _ _ I-CW
bouquet _ _ B-CW
. _ _ O

# id d0788d3e-c179-433f-b049-d510935260d6	domain=train
alexander _ _ O
is _ _ O
credited _ _ O
with _ _ O
laying _ _ O
the _ _ O
foundations _ _ O
of _ _ O
music _ _ O
education _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
dallas _ _ B-LOC
public _ _ O
schools _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id c9d5d127-4363-4e3d-b370-619fb334969b	domain=train
cooktop _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
top _ _ O
cooking _ _ O
surface _ _ O
on _ _ O
a _ _ O
kitchen _ _ B-PROD
stove _ _ I-PROD

# id e58b573f-5064-4bf7-9b82-97371d72a772	domain=train
galindians _ _ O
were _ _ O
two _ _ O
distinct _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
now _ _ O
extinct _ _ O
, _ _ O
tribes _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
balts _ _ B-PER
. _ _ O

# id 92d2f1a3-f71c-4206-a4db-b9b751555cec	domain=train
sp _ _ O
3606 _ _ O
is _ _ O
privately _ _ O
owned _ _ O
as _ _ O
part _ _ O
of _ _ O
a _ _ O
collection _ _ O
of _ _ O
former _ _ O
railroad _ _ O
cars _ _ O
in _ _ O
rocklin _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 410ccd59-8b41-47e9-a640-11cb919b7541	domain=train
made _ _ O
part _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
jilin–shulan _ _ B-LOC
railway _ _ I-LOC
in _ _ O
1941 _ _ O

# id c1c3b3a1-e08b-4290-8953-fd051e624a34	domain=train
in _ _ O
1485 _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
area _ _ O
was _ _ O
included _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
grand _ _ B-LOC
duchy _ _ I-LOC
of _ _ I-LOC
moscow _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 1d035ec5-a647-4c61-8a42-4d0d2fc53e58	domain=train
he _ _ O
then _ _ O
spent _ _ O
8 _ _ O
seasons _ _ O
with _ _ O
fc _ _ B-GRP
volendam _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
for _ _ O
whom _ _ O
he _ _ O
scored _ _ O
48 _ _ O
goals _ _ O
in _ _ O
218 _ _ O
games _ _ O
in _ _ O
all _ _ O
competitions _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 155f5c33-f9b1-4331-96f5-f9a27300dc84	domain=train
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
a _ _ O
member _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
federalist _ _ B-GRP
party _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id ba97741c-20ab-4300-8523-2466b239c00e	domain=train
renninger _ _ O
considered _ _ O
the _ _ O
game _ _ O
too _ _ O
easy _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
believed _ _ O
that _ _ O
the _ _ O
links _ _ B-CW
was _ _ O
superior _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5f9de98a-088b-4cf3-afee-c00f204a8802	domain=train
senegal _ _ B-LOC
has _ _ O
also _ _ O
seen _ _ O
an _ _ O
increase _ _ O
in _ _ O
life _ _ O
expectancy _ _ O
at _ _ O
birth _ _ O
from _ _ O
57 _ _ O
% _ _ O
in _ _ O
2000 _ _ O
to _ _ O
67.38 _ _ O
% _ _ O
in _ _ O
2017 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f103cd1b-67a2-4144-8e8f-d0be85463cc4	domain=train
president _ _ O
in _ _ O
: _ _ O
hot _ _ B-CW
shots! _ _ I-CW
part _ _ I-CW
deux _ _ I-CW
( _ _ O
film _ _ O
, _ _ O
1993 _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id 83529579-3cdc-498a-960b-68691ee8891a	domain=train
randolph _ _ O
was _ _ O
born _ _ O
in _ _ O
nashville _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id c20e4ee8-9188-48cf-8cdd-e9d9b08697b4	domain=train
during _ _ O
his _ _ O
nine _ _ O
year _ _ O
professional _ _ O
career _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
appeared _ _ O
almost _ _ O
exclusively _ _ O
for _ _ O
local _ _ O
s.c. _ _ B-GRP
braga _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 2af0253d-fac7-43c4-8274-2cc6347a2954	domain=train
tex _ _ B-PER
beneke _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
1914 _ _ O
– _ _ O
2000 _ _ O
) _ _ O
, _ _ O
big _ _ O
band _ _ O
saxophonist _ _ O
, _ _ O
singer _ _ O
, _ _ O
bandleader _ _ O

# id 645b212e-eeac-470e-a312-cac7d1357ac9	domain=train
hymn _ _ B-CW
to _ _ I-CW
germany _ _ I-CW
for _ _ O
medium _ _ O
voice _ _ O
and _ _ O
piano _ _ O
; _ _ O
words _ _ O
by _ _ O
rudolf _ _ B-PER
alexander _ _ I-PER
schröder _ _ I-PER

# id 23318259-66b0-4d0b-a9a5-00400496f623	domain=train
uk _ _ O
: _ _ O
leicester _ _ B-LOC
: _ _ O
mini _ _ O
excavators _ _ O
; _ _ O
peterlee _ _ B-LOC
: _ _ O
articulated _ _ O
dump _ _ O
trucks _ _ O
; _ _ O
peterborough _ _ B-LOC
: _ _ O
engines _ _ O
; _ _ O
larne _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
belfast _ _ B-LOC
: _ _ O
generating _ _ O
sets _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 743ff7d7-6678-46de-8b47-b26d88e13a3a	domain=train
u.s. _ _ O
swimmer _ _ O
scott _ _ B-PER
weltz _ _ I-PER
finished _ _ O
fifth _ _ O
in _ _ O
2 _ _ O
: _ _ O
09.02 _ _ O
to _ _ O
hold _ _ O
off _ _ O
his _ _ O
teammate _ _ O
clark _ _ B-PER
burckle _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
2 _ _ O
: _ _ O
09.25 _ _ O
) _ _ O
by _ _ O
23 _ _ O
hundredths _ _ O
of _ _ O
a _ _ O
second _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id c4f4bbb6-1219-44fb-a7fa-32c1bef168ae	domain=train
similar _ _ O
to _ _ O
many _ _ O
other _ _ O
forms _ _ O
of _ _ O
divination _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
diviner _ _ O
casts _ _ O
table _ _ B-PROD
salt _ _ I-PROD
crystals _ _ O
into _ _ O
the _ _ O
air _ _ O
and _ _ O
interprets _ _ O
the _ _ O
patterns _ _ O
as _ _ O
it _ _ O
falls _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
ground _ _ O
or _ _ O
travels _ _ O
through _ _ O
the _ _ O
air _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5c950575-739b-4a0a-bf07-a27f13be2eef	domain=train
the _ _ O
main _ _ O
campus _ _ O
of _ _ O
mountains _ _ B-GRP
of _ _ I-GRP
the _ _ I-GRP
moon _ _ I-GRP
university _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
private _ _ O
university _ _ O
, _ _ O
is _ _ O
located _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
city _ _ O
center _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 377afdb4-e9ee-434a-9ce8-382b02b1be5f	domain=train
the _ _ O
movie _ _ O
was _ _ O
reported _ _ O
to _ _ O
be _ _ O
inspired _ _ O
by _ _ O
sholay _ _ B-CW
. _ _ O

# id 9523ef45-4c9e-45fe-a6c4-ca89e7c32a8a	domain=train
blanchard _ _ O
scored _ _ O
his _ _ O
first _ _ O
goal _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
club _ _ O
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
1 _ _ O
– _ _ O
1 _ _ O
draw _ _ O
with _ _ O
crawley _ _ B-GRP
town _ _ I-GRP
f.c. _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id fa4f252a-ac11-44bd-a311-519352c9189c	domain=train
; _ _ O
voiced _ _ O
by _ _ O
brenda _ _ B-PER
vaccaro _ _ I-PER
in _ _ O
season _ _ O
1 _ _ O
; _ _ O
rhea _ _ B-PER
perlman _ _ I-PER
in _ _ O
season _ _ O
2 _ _ O

# id 6813d769-9415-42e8-a8c6-fcdfc16ee78b	domain=train
andrew _ _ O
has _ _ O
also _ _ O
been _ _ O
a _ _ O
member _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
dallas _ _ B-GRP
cowboys _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
new _ _ B-GRP
york _ _ I-GRP
jets _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
philadelphia _ _ B-GRP
eagles _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
minnesota _ _ B-GRP
vikings _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 24839afc-8e5e-45fd-8554-b209ac71094b	domain=train
in _ _ O
1979 _ _ O
, _ _ O
under _ _ O
her _ _ O
direction _ _ O
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
documentary _ _ O
about _ _ O
simone _ _ B-PER
de _ _ I-PER
beauvoir _ _ I-PER
appeared _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id c61e010d-a316-45c7-b82a-d7af321b9ed6	domain=train
the _ _ O
rolling _ _ O
chassis _ _ O
is _ _ O
delivered _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
commercial _ _ O
body _ _ O
maker _ _ O
, _ _ O
coachbuilder _ _ B-CORP
, _ _ O
or _ _ O
bulk _ _ O
transporter _ _ O
on _ _ O
its _ _ O
own _ _ O
wheels _ _ O
, _ _ O
under _ _ O
its _ _ O
own _ _ O
power _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 2f4ed29c-69dd-4cf1-b7d1-022b9fcbffc5	domain=train
emi _ _ B-CORP
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
music _ _ O
and _ _ O
electronics _ _ O
group _ _ O
of _ _ O
companies _ _ O

# id 359cfeab-fcc0-4fbb-828c-9e48550bde42	domain=train
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
located _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
municipality _ _ O
of _ _ O
rakovica _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id c60699fd-c73a-42d1-886b-895080a65e45	domain=train
coffee _ _ B-PROD
would _ _ O
be _ _ O
included _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
same _ _ O
manner _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e60ef70e-778b-4c31-a189-6db58ca1c9b0	domain=train
joseph _ _ B-PER
whitworth _ _ I-PER
devised _ _ O
a _ _ O
series _ _ O
of _ _ O
standards _ _ O
for _ _ O
engineering _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
built _ _ O
a _ _ O
rifle _ _ O
with _ _ O
an _ _ O
accurately _ _ O
rifled _ _ O
barrel _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ac192718-e49d-4b0e-9d4f-8d81cd76ff51	domain=train
the _ _ O
third _ _ O
, _ _ O
scherzo _ _ B-CW
like _ _ O
movement _ _ O
, _ _ O
has _ _ O
an _ _ O
easy _ _ O
spirit _ _ O
yet _ _ O
is _ _ O
full _ _ O
of _ _ O
complex _ _ O
rhythms _ _ O
and _ _ O
interwoven _ _ O
textures _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id eea75781-525b-4677-b046-5341c3d1e044	domain=train
a _ _ O
zoetrope _ _ B-PROD
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
device _ _ O
used _ _ O
for _ _ O
animation _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 698aaac2-19f5-404f-9ba1-9ce3e849bb12	domain=train
he _ _ O
published _ _ O
first _ _ O
illustration _ _ O
in _ _ O
lui _ _ B-CW
, _ _ O
l'expansion _ _ B-CW
and _ _ O
cosmopolitan _ _ B-CW
. _ _ O

# id a79b1571-0dce-4a33-8cd4-2b71ef01bac1	domain=train
a _ _ O
saddle _ _ B-PROD
chair _ _ I-PROD
encourages _ _ O
this _ _ O
natural _ _ O
posture _ _ O
, _ _ O
which _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
same _ _ O
as _ _ O
when _ _ O
lying _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
side _ _ O
while _ _ O
sleeping _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 52179eae-e92d-4054-a2e4-8c7bb79b0269	domain=train
the _ _ O
demo _ _ O
was _ _ O
later _ _ O
released _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
quadrophenia _ _ B-CW
box _ _ O
set _ _ O
of _ _ O
2011 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 1da7f478-d62e-4b65-9b7c-01ecd3b52c7e	domain=train
former _ _ O
professional _ _ O
football _ _ O
player _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
new _ _ B-GRP
york _ _ I-GRP
jets _ _ I-GRP

# id d043feb4-46e0-41e6-8953-aac01de8367c	domain=train
more _ _ O
recently _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
church _ _ O
has _ _ O
faced _ _ O
an _ _ O
increased _ _ O
demand _ _ O
for _ _ O
suburb _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
a _ _ O
decline _ _ O
in _ _ O
attendance _ _ O
to _ _ O
inner _ _ B-LOC
city _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id 6ebed57b-8bce-47b1-97c2-d4dd0cf047f3	domain=train
ocean _ _ B-LOC
city _ _ I-LOC
retains _ _ O
its _ _ O
ban _ _ O
but _ _ O
exempts _ _ O
persons _ _ O
with _ _ O
a _ _ O
concealed _ _ O
weapons _ _ O
permit _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ O
ban _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ce106989-6093-4683-ab9b-e1a979ae654a	domain=train
the _ _ O
book _ _ O
's _ _ O
sometimes _ _ O
cynical _ _ O
humor _ _ O
has _ _ O
been _ _ O
described _ _ O
as _ _ O
similar _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ B-CORP
onion _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id b5b9abef-edf0-4a3c-9e43-dac89423c29c	domain=train
since _ _ O
2008 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
has _ _ O
been _ _ O
the _ _ O
senior _ _ O
vice _ _ O
president _ _ O
of _ _ O
disney _ _ B-CORP
television _ _ I-CORP
animation _ _ I-CORP
( _ _ O
owned _ _ O
by _ _ O
the _ _ B-GRP
walt _ _ I-GRP
disney _ _ I-GRP
company _ _ I-GRP
) _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 08421dc6-8af7-488a-b6bc-8f239b6ea9ff	domain=train
the _ _ O
song _ _ O
featured _ _ O
chris _ _ B-PER
trousdale _ _ I-PER
from _ _ O
dream _ _ B-GRP
street _ _ I-GRP
and _ _ O
received _ _ O
high _ _ O
rotation _ _ O
on _ _ O
radio _ _ B-CORP
disney _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id f02d29f2-46aa-4c65-a4eb-bd1b98cb568e	domain=train
nostradameus _ _ B-PER
( _ _ O
paul _ _ B-PER
rugg _ _ I-PER
) _ _ O
claims _ _ O
to _ _ O
be _ _ O
able _ _ O
to _ _ O
predictiate _ _ O
the _ _ O
future _ _ O
, _ _ O
though _ _ O
he _ _ O
is _ _ O
proven _ _ O
wrong _ _ O
on _ _ O
occasion _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 867d142e-fda6-4eb0-92a8-2e12d255d28f	domain=train
a _ _ O
statue _ _ O
of _ _ O
benjamin _ _ B-PER
franklin _ _ I-PER
was _ _ O
displayed _ _ O
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
entrance _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 0ac6aa66-2e64-4d7a-beb9-f24618bf25a3	domain=train
rolls _ _ O
collected _ _ O
art _ _ O
including _ _ O
sketches _ _ O
by _ _ O
henry _ _ B-PER
fuseli _ _ I-PER
and _ _ O
illuminated _ _ O
manuscripts _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 6e4e2a4e-4aea-44d6-af9d-3869be324f65	domain=train
jorge _ _ B-PER
martínez _ _ I-PER
de _ _ I-PER
hoyos _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
el _ _ B-CW
abuelo _ _ I-CW
y _ _ I-CW
yo _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
1993 _ _ O
) _ _ O
and _ _ O
ignacio _ _ B-PER
lópez _ _ I-PER
tarso _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
de _ _ B-CW
pocas, _ _ I-CW
pocas _ _ I-CW
pulgas _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
2003 _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id d7ec4602-e4bd-426a-b970-920b5e637d9d	domain=train
it _ _ O
became _ _ O
widely _ _ O
ridiculed _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
soup _ _ I-CW
. _ _ O

# id b6a7a0cd-614f-42c0-bb95-658d5495d926	domain=train
in _ _ O
1941 _ _ O
she _ _ O
was _ _ O
appointed _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
staff _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
royal _ _ B-GRP
academy _ _ I-GRP
of _ _ I-GRP
music _ _ I-GRP
where _ _ O
, _ _ O
starting _ _ O
with _ _ O
seven _ _ O
students _ _ O
, _ _ O
she _ _ O
built _ _ O
the _ _ O
drama _ _ O
course _ _ O
to _ _ O
70 _ _ O
students _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id b17fd0e0-2c87-41eb-9543-e7430d1f2fd0	domain=train
fantasea _ _ O
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
1978 _ _ O
surf _ _ O
movie _ _ O
with _ _ O
shaun _ _ B-PER
tomson _ _ I-PER

# id 49cf0500-b155-4ee6-9cc1-154d1ebc3d0f	domain=train
he _ _ O
also _ _ O
served _ _ O
as _ _ O
a _ _ O
fundraiser _ _ O
and _ _ O
consultant _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
democratic _ _ B-CORP
national _ _ I-CORP
committee _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id e10a5e32-bbe1-4401-9670-865bcc297843	domain=train
top _ _ O
4 _ _ O
: _ _ O
don't _ _ B-CW
stop _ _ I-CW
me _ _ I-CW
now _ _ I-CW
queen _ _ B-GRP
( _ _ O
pop _ _ O
jazz _ _ O
; _ _ O
choreographer _ _ O
: _ _ O
tba _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id b432033d-292d-4665-8c37-bfe1501cf9fb	domain=train
celebration _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
compilation _ _ B-CW
album _ _ I-CW
by _ _ O
switzerland _ _ B-LOC
singer _ _ O
dj _ _ B-PER
bobo _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
released _ _ O
in _ _ O
2002 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 25ef42ad-43f9-4f7a-b343-31965180cab6	domain=train
karta _ _ O
bink _ _ O
was _ _ O
born _ _ O
in _ _ O
commewijne _ _ B-LOC
district _ _ I-LOC
in _ _ O
about _ _ O
1972 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 4be4651d-a098-4583-97d1-57ce39911e5e	domain=train
however _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
party _ _ O
began _ _ O
to _ _ O
move _ _ O
away _ _ O
from _ _ O
revolutionary _ _ B-LOC
socialism _ _ I-LOC
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
turn _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
20th _ _ O
century _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ee86c829-e6f3-488c-bb7e-5c4f2f5a8cb5	domain=train
hanriot _ _ O
h _ _ O
. _ _ O
230 _ _ O
was _ _ O
a _ _ O
france _ _ B-LOC
twin _ _ O
engined _ _ O
advanced _ _ O
trainer _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 7a447fbb-9038-4883-bbdc-e7a8c7d33a27	domain=train
mailen _ _ B-PER
auroux _ _ I-PER
maría _ _ B-PER
irigoyen _ _ I-PER
6 _ _ O
– _ _ O
1 _ _ O
, _ _ O
2 _ _ O
– _ _ O
6 _ _ O
, _ _ O
[ _ _ O
10 _ _ O
– _ _ O
5 _ _ O
] _ _ O

# id 8e90915c-7a21-453d-b182-26f9aad8102d	domain=train
the _ _ O
great _ _ B-LOC
western _ _ I-LOC
highway _ _ I-LOC
and _ _ O
the _ _ O
railway _ _ O
defined _ _ O
the _ _ O
northern _ _ O
limit _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 5b308395-7a2a-4be4-81ad-9f9aedfdd2f6	domain=train
john _ _ B-PER
patterson _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
former _ _ O
pitcher _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
arizona _ _ B-GRP
diamondbacks _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 0c4da2da-64cc-4e03-91fb-5503c788f6fe	domain=train
they _ _ O
also _ _ O
manufacture _ _ O
electronic _ _ O
carillons _ _ O
, _ _ O
street _ _ B-PROD
clock _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
glockenspiels _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
monuments _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 165110aa-ed87-4d14-be74-ed8e4cb69cfd	domain=train
the _ _ O
product _ _ O
range _ _ O
includes _ _ O
bag _ _ B-PROD
and _ _ O
suitcase _ _ B-PROD
. _ _ O

# id bf220c75-763f-4975-aa43-12ebb8202d21	domain=train
its _ _ O
design _ _ O
is _ _ O
based _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
209 _ _ B-PROD
series _ _ I-PROD
. _ _ O

# id b7c6fdbb-ee47-4a50-af50-2deb399fd465	domain=train
its _ _ O
northern _ _ O
border _ _ O
follows _ _ O
interstate _ _ B-LOC
81 _ _ I-LOC
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
its _ _ O
eastern _ _ O
border _ _ O
follows _ _ O
pennsylvania _ _ B-LOC
route _ _ I-LOC
39 _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id ae6bbf02-5db7-4226-94c8-963952d4a836	domain=train
father _ _ O
émile _ _ B-PER
petitot _ _ I-PER
describes _ _ O
his _ _ O
reception _ _ O
in _ _ O
1862 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 20b0f3e2-294d-44b0-85cb-5bfd16fd9c6a	domain=train
c _ _ O
37b _ _ O
or _ _ O
gulfstream _ _ B-PROD
g550 _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
business _ _ O
jet _ _ O

# id cec12228-24a1-466b-a9cf-17c17d052ad1	domain=train
file _ _ O
: _ _ O
sauna _ _ O
stove _ _ O
narvi _ _ O
02 _ _ O
. _ _ O
jpg _ _ O
| _ _ O
wood _ _ O
burning _ _ O
sauna _ _ B-LOC
stove _ _ O
, _ _ O
finland _ _ B-LOC

# id c1e1d04c-03eb-4c15-aa2d-8e1a4273be67	domain=train
capcom _ _ B-CORP
purchased _ _ O
the _ _ O
intellectual _ _ O
property _ _ O
in _ _ O
2012 _ _ O
and _ _ O
provided _ _ O
funding _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
project _ _ O
, _ _ O
reimagining _ _ O
it _ _ O
as _ _ O
an _ _ O
action-adventure _ _ B-CW
game _ _ I-CW
for _ _ O
release _ _ O
on _ _ O
multiple _ _ O
platforms _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id ce5fb3e1-0ace-4650-8a47-13a7fe851491	domain=train
in _ _ O
1985 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
tried _ _ O
a _ _ O
comeback _ _ O
with _ _ O
blue _ _ B-GRP
bulls _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
only _ _ O
played _ _ O
in _ _ O
three _ _ O
provincial _ _ O
matches _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id c322968a-1061-4244-b751-4c84ee3dce55	domain=train
this _ _ O
chiefly _ _ O
consisted _ _ O
of _ _ O
coal _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
area _ _ O
north _ _ O
of _ _ O
llanelli _ _ B-LOC
and _ _ O
around _ _ O
saundersfoot _ _ B-LOC
. _ _ O

# id eeba9db6-b08f-44aa-837e-1ff7462b9b7a	domain=train
they _ _ O
currently _ _ O
play _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
macedonian _ _ B-GRP
first _ _ I-GRP
league _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 811516cf-ac9a-4f45-9f81-7181e4c4d04d	domain=train
# _ _ O
solo _ _ O
( _ _ O
sandy _ _ B-PER
denny _ _ I-PER
) _ _ O
( _ _ O
sandy _ _ O
denny _ _ O
, _ _ O
from _ _ O
like _ _ B-CW
an _ _ I-CW
old _ _ I-CW
fashioned _ _ I-CW
waltz _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
1974 _ _ O
) _ _ O
– _ _ O
4 _ _ O
: _ _ O
46 _ _ O

# id b99cffdd-988b-4faf-a0a4-cbd51fceaa84	domain=train
he _ _ O
finished _ _ O
third _ _ O
, _ _ O
behind _ _ O
liberal _ _ B-GRP
party _ _ I-GRP
of _ _ I-GRP
canada _ _ I-GRP
nancy _ _ B-PER
karetak-lindell _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id dbfceb6e-7926-4191-9dfa-ac2ebb376e5d	domain=train
( _ _ O
cannata _ _ O
stayed _ _ O
until _ _ O
1981 _ _ O
, _ _ O
returning _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
river _ _ B-CW
of _ _ I-CW
dreams _ _ I-CW
recording _ _ O
sessions _ _ O
in _ _ O
1993 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id aa5c8bac-7d7b-4123-9f50-e9a2912bd07b	domain=train
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
neighbor _ _ O
to _ _ O
high _ _ O
carihuairazo _ _ B-LOC
volcano _ _ I-LOC
. _ _ O

# id d31debd9-130b-46dc-92e4-06fcb9623ed8	domain=train
the _ _ O
keypad _ _ B-PROD
lock _ _ O
feature _ _ O
found _ _ O
on _ _ O
most _ _ O
mobile _ _ O
phones _ _ O
is _ _ O
intended _ _ O
to _ _ O
help _ _ O
prevent _ _ O
accidental _ _ O
dialing _ _ O
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
is _ _ O
often _ _ O
so _ _ O
trivial _ _ O
that _ _ O
the _ _ O
keypad _ _ O
is _ _ O
easily _ _ O
pocket _ _ O
unlocked _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id f2c98dd8-3d83-4021-b025-426a6cd4e39e	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
even _ _ O
featured _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
irish _ _ B-GRP
independent _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id ce468751-ae41-4140-8c2a-87fc244352a3	domain=train
hershey _ _ B-PROD
bar _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
their _ _ O
most _ _ O
iconic _ _ O
product _ _ O

# id 32b0a202-7178-4e70-8250-5e4ccd364027	domain=train
c’ _ _ O
est _ _ O
ma _ _ O
fête _ _ O
– _ _ O
it's _ _ B-CW
my _ _ I-CW
party _ _ I-CW

# id b821d46e-acd6-4839-93d9-49887cdf6701	domain=train
in _ _ O
2015 _ _ O
the _ _ O
team _ _ O
switched _ _ O
from _ _ O
ktm _ _ B-CORP
to _ _ O
husqvarna _ _ B-CORP
motorcycles _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id e0da21e6-6ec8-4092-a6fa-64b4a73639a6	domain=train
evelyn _ _ B-PER
keyes _ _ I-PER
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
bit _ _ O
part _ _ O
( _ _ O
uncredited _ _ O
) _ _ O

# id 4cc312c1-4f9d-4dbb-b06a-ea4c01204aeb	domain=train
she _ _ O
attended _ _ O
public _ _ O
schools _ _ O
in _ _ O
worcester _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
went _ _ O
on _ _ O
to _ _ O
attend _ _ O
wellesley _ _ B-GRP
college _ _ I-GRP
in _ _ O
1902 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 06239085-1c99-4c89-94a7-53ed6e6c1bf5	domain=train
in _ _ O
1988 _ _ O
, _ _ O
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
adapted _ _ O
into _ _ O
a _ _ O
funny _ _ B-CW
farm _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
starring _ _ O
chevy _ _ B-PER
chase _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id 1bbc03a2-1382-41bc-a929-f9724a4fd46c	domain=train
its _ _ O
basement _ _ O
hosts _ _ O
kitchen _ _ O
facilities _ _ O
while _ _ O
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
ground _ _ O
floor _ _ O
is _ _ O
located _ _ O
an _ _ O
internet _ _ B-CORP
café _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 39b7ee5d-0936-48e8-8ff0-9b0748ae9dff	domain=train
victor _ _ B-PER
svendsen _ _ I-PER
11 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
, _ _ O
11 _ _ O
– _ _ O
7 _ _ O
, _ _ O
8 _ _ O
– _ _ O
11 _ _ O
, _ _ O
10 _ _ O
– _ _ O
12 _ _ O
, _ _ O
11 _ _ O
– _ _ O
4 _ _ O

# id 655df740-053b-4c66-a8b5-04303d7659d7	domain=train
sky _ _ O
leads _ _ O
the _ _ O
cubs _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
mudflats _ _ O
to _ _ O
dig _ _ O
up _ _ O
clam _ _ B-PROD
hiding _ _ O
under _ _ O
the _ _ O
mud _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 44614a07-196c-429d-a843-3ed6b065bed8	domain=train
indian _ _ B-PROD
locomotive _ _ I-PROD
class _ _ I-PROD
wap-7 _ _ I-PROD
locomotive _ _ O
powers _ _ O
the _ _ O
train _ _ O
end _ _ O
to _ _ O
end _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 26c96035-8464-4894-b782-2a2d1628ee09	domain=train
he _ _ O
made _ _ O
his _ _ O
debut _ _ O
for _ _ O
sogndal _ _ B-GRP
fotball _ _ I-GRP
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
1 _ _ O
1 _ _ O
draw _ _ O
against _ _ O
ik _ _ B-GRP
start _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 76a1702d-fc9a-48ee-8d86-7e17b2c9e9c2	domain=train
weight _ _ O
tax _ _ O
deduction _ _ O
for _ _ O
plug-in _ _ B-PROD
hybrid _ _ I-PROD
introduced _ _ O

# id e05c59d6-6895-44ee-9cba-23d356a72a81	domain=train
for _ _ O
maximum _ _ O
flavor _ _ O
and _ _ O
aroma _ _ O
, _ _ O
as _ _ O
in _ _ O
mulled _ _ B-PROD
wine _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
zest _ _ O
is _ _ O
simply _ _ O
cut _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ O
fruit _ _ O
with _ _ O
a _ _ O
knife _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 096c6717-1111-432a-a3e3-a7cfe95f97d5	domain=train
remains _ _ O
of _ _ O
copper _ _ B-PROD
smelting _ _ O
sites _ _ O
and _ _ O
open _ _ O
air _ _ O
copper _ _ O
mines _ _ O
were _ _ O
investigated _ _ O
in _ _ O
1984 _ _ O
– _ _ O
1985 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 3cffa39f-ae38-45cd-bb9f-a9c74b331a0e	domain=train
after _ _ O
the _ _ O
film _ _ O
's _ _ O
release _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
song _ _ O
became _ _ O
a _ _ O
hit _ _ O
and _ _ O
a _ _ O
jazz _ _ B-CW
standard _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
has _ _ O
been _ _ O
widely _ _ O
covered _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 9c6d319a-4230-4064-acf2-1491cba9cb13	domain=train
the _ _ O
airport _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
hub _ _ O
for _ _ O
both _ _ O
united _ _ B-CORP
airlines _ _ I-CORP
and _ _ O
frontier _ _ B-CORP
airlines _ _ I-CORP
and _ _ O
a _ _ O
base _ _ O
for _ _ O
southwest _ _ B-CORP
airlines _ _ I-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 853f0aeb-6a8a-40bd-b827-d7ca5920e1e2	domain=train
a _ _ O
few _ _ O
days _ _ O
later _ _ O
, _ _ O
harry _ _ B-PER
houdini _ _ I-PER
comes _ _ O
to _ _ O
town _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 6f5968dd-bf70-425f-b19f-8224868b13cd	domain=train
according _ _ O
to _ _ O
his _ _ O
employment _ _ O
record _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
worked _ _ O
as _ _ O
a _ _ O
loader _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
united _ _ B-CORP
parcel _ _ I-CORP
service _ _ I-CORP
from _ _ O
1983 _ _ O
to _ _ O
1997 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 3df8ae58-ab37-49c2-b4df-e8d1755d282a	domain=train
the _ _ O
album _ _ O
features _ _ O
six _ _ O
different _ _ O
covers _ _ O
, _ _ O
depicting _ _ O
each _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
various _ _ O
band _ _ O
members _ _ O
death _ _ B-PROD
mask _ _ I-PROD
. _ _ O

# id 8132d76d-f3e1-408a-aafc-741abcf3686b	domain=train
in _ _ O
2012 _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
chevrolet _ _ B-PROD
cobalt _ _ I-PROD
was _ _ O
added _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
production _ _ O
line _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id c35465ac-bb08-4dda-96a2-b2da8f9892ae	domain=train
goya _ _ O
learned _ _ O
from _ _ O
these _ _ O
sources _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
from _ _ O
rembrandt _ _ B-PER
, _ _ O
some _ _ O
of _ _ O
whose _ _ O
prints _ _ O
he _ _ O
owned _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 2a37364b-b17b-411a-88b6-641b43de5ec0	domain=train
from _ _ O
1962 _ _ O
to _ _ O
1965 _ _ O
he _ _ O
was _ _ O
ambassador _ _ O
in _ _ O
bonn _ _ B-LOC
( _ _ O
germany _ _ B-LOC
) _ _ O

# id 9cc468d1-0936-4ab6-9ce1-e7b62dc66652	domain=train
in _ _ O
2017 _ _ O
, _ _ O
he _ _ O
moved _ _ O
to _ _ O
helsingin _ _ B-GRP
jalkapalloklubi _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 7b50790d-d0b7-4451-82fe-872b7dfb5860	domain=train
torchlight _ _ B-CW
iii _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
2020 _ _ O
action _ _ O
role _ _ O
playing _ _ O
game _ _ O

# id c227982a-7dc9-4d5f-87dd-2524d246ebd4	domain=train
it _ _ O
stars _ _ O
shaina _ _ B-PER
magdayao _ _ I-PER
in _ _ O
the _ _ O
title _ _ O
role _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id b373e9e8-a264-4ac8-a3bd-6330c062a9ff	domain=train
as _ _ O
for _ _ O
wheat _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
another _ _ O
staple _ _ O
, _ _ O
it _ _ O
took _ _ O
another _ _ O
three _ _ O
or _ _ O
four _ _ O
thousand _ _ O
years _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id e4a1a9c6-64ea-4c40-9663-8fe38789c065	domain=train
he _ _ O
moved _ _ O
to _ _ O
peru _ _ B-LOC
for _ _ O
eight _ _ O
years _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 1339ff53-fdd0-4c3f-a812-95af8dfc0fdb	domain=train
deutch _ _ O
was _ _ O
born _ _ O
in _ _ O
los _ _ B-LOC
angeles _ _ I-LOC
, _ _ O
california _ _ B-LOC
, _ _ O
to _ _ O
actress _ _ O
lea _ _ B-PER
thompson _ _ I-PER
and _ _ O
director _ _ O
howard _ _ B-PER
deutch _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id c5fa941d-87a1-4632-9f4d-ce41aff19ed3	domain=train
ferdinand _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
main _ _ O
character _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
story _ _ I-CW
of _ _ I-CW
ferdinand _ _ I-CW

# id 5e05617c-f266-4779-be8a-558b7cce63f6	domain=train
in _ _ O
1997 _ _ O
, _ _ O
bbc _ _ B-CORP
radio _ _ I-CORP
4 _ _ I-CORP
broadcast _ _ O
a _ _ O
dramatization _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
story _ _ O
in _ _ O
six _ _ O
half _ _ O
hour _ _ O
episodes _ _ O
, _ _ O
later _ _ O
re _ _ O
edited _ _ O
into _ _ O
three _ _ O
hour _ _ O
long _ _ O
episodes _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 6d075e28-2bfe-42c3-929f-a27de694a242	domain=train
lau _ _ O
would _ _ O
later _ _ O
turn _ _ O
down _ _ O
the _ _ O
role _ _ O
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
wang _ _ B-PER
xueqi _ _ I-PER
was _ _ O
cast _ _ O
instead _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 00f3ff5c-ef9a-4798-ae0a-fd571d83291b	domain=train
he _ _ O
moved _ _ O
to _ _ O
stockport _ _ B-GRP
county _ _ I-GRP
f.c. _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
playing _ _ O
50 _ _ O
times _ _ O
before _ _ O
joining _ _ O
tranmere _ _ B-GRP
rovers _ _ I-GRP
f.c. _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id 17c69c91-b92b-46e1-9f80-70aa894cde7a	domain=train
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
the _ _ O
first _ _ O
major _ _ O
white _ _ O
rap _ _ O
record _ _ O
, _ _ O
predating _ _ O
the _ _ O
recording _ _ O
of _ _ O
blondie _ _ B-GRP
rapture _ _ B-CW
by _ _ O
six _ _ O
months _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 8c41b541-93f5-4da4-90e5-d26504543ded	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
rebuilt _ _ O
by _ _ O
benjamin _ _ B-PER
ferrey _ _ I-PER
in _ _ O
1856 _ _ O
, _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
site _ _ O
of _ _ O
an _ _ O
earlier _ _ O
church _ _ O
, _ _ O
but _ _ O
closed _ _ O
in _ _ O
1970 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 14cb4331-7a77-4b93-b46d-9d247c94b8b3	domain=train
horatio _ _ B-PER
allen _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
designed _ _ O
world _ _ O
's _ _ O
first _ _ O
articulated _ _ B-PROD
locomotive _ _ I-PROD
in _ _ O
1832 _ _ O

# id d8189208-9e60-4c96-9c4e-116baac7028f	domain=train
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
following _ _ O
year _ _ O
a _ _ O
new _ _ O
car _ _ O
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
ferrari _ _ B-PROD
412 _ _ I-PROD
t2 _ _ I-PROD
came _ _ O
out _ _ O
which _ _ O
received _ _ O
many _ _ O
changes _ _ O
that _ _ O
aided _ _ O
both _ _ O
aero _ _ O
and _ _ O
safety _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 16b969a9-52cd-45c0-b845-b32691ad1896	domain=train
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
sung _ _ O
then _ _ O
by _ _ O
john _ _ B-PER
henry _ _ I-PER
johnstone _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
it _ _ O
was _ _ O
later _ _ O
a _ _ O
favourite _ _ O
piece _ _ O
of _ _ O
charles _ _ B-PER
incledon _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O

# id bd5aa3f7-90e7-4c70-8aa7-794f90d49407	domain=train
he _ _ O
played _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
miami _ _ B-GRP
dolphins _ _ I-GRP
in _ _ O
1966 _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id a7d5c593-a910-47de-a6c9-2c8da461c10f	domain=train
sugar _ _ O
sprinkled _ _ O
on _ _ O
cut _ _ O
fruit _ _ O
will _ _ O
draw _ _ O
out _ _ O
the _ _ O
water _ _ O
through _ _ O
hydrophilia _ _ O
, _ _ O
making _ _ O
the _ _ O
fruit _ _ O
mushy _ _ O
and _ _ O
wet _ _ O
, _ _ O
as _ _ O
in _ _ O
a _ _ O
common _ _ O
strawberry _ _ O
compote _ _ B-PROD
recipe _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 19184d64-c797-45cd-a414-5489eccc3714	domain=train
the _ _ B-CW
ant _ _ I-CW
and _ _ I-CW
the _ _ I-CW
aardvark _ _ I-CW
, _ _ O
a _ _ O
cartoon _ _ O
series _ _ O
that _ _ O
inspired _ _ O
the _ _ O
game _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 340ade13-d7c0-42fd-9cb6-4066d1b8f8f0	domain=train
the _ _ O
south _ _ O
gallery _ _ O
was _ _ O
extended _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
east _ _ O
end _ _ O
and _ _ O
the _ _ O
pulpit _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
by _ _ O
then _ _ O
three _ _ O
decker _ _ O
, _ _ O
was _ _ O
relocated _ _ O
to _ _ O
the _ _ O
centre _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
nave _ _ O
aisle _ _ O
at _ _ O
the _ _ O
east _ _ O
end _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 3a681027-b539-4193-9a3b-7c54fb73da84	domain=train
she _ _ O
was _ _ O
the _ _ O
chairman _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
standing _ _ O
commission _ _ O
on _ _ O
the _ _ O
history _ _ O
of _ _ O
cartography _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
international _ _ B-GRP
cartographic _ _ I-GRP
association _ _ I-GRP
. _ _ O

# id dd27a059-524a-4822-b533-e3fadbf89bb7	domain=train
two _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
awards _ _ O
go _ _ O
to _ _ O
lundgaard _ _ B-CORP
& _ _ I-CORP
tranberg _ _ I-CORP
and _ _ O
one _ _ O
goes _ _ O
to _ _ O
3xn _ _ B-CORP
. _ _ O

# id 9ca63b66-d96b-4332-891e-920bdb26ed32	domain=train
# _ _ O
runaway _ _ B-CW
( _ _ O
del _ _ B-PER
shannon _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
max _ _ B-PER
crook _ _ I-PER
) _ _ O
– _ _ O
2 _ _ O
: _ _ O
19 _ _ O

# id e2bab9b4-956b-4d94-97a3-53d559b54e60	domain=train
a _ _ O
force _ _ O
play _ _ O
provided _ _ O
the _ _ O
second _ _ O
out _ _ O
of _ _ O
the _ _ O
inning _ _ O
but _ _ O
boog _ _ B-PER
powell _ _ I-PER
single _ _ O
drove _ _ O
in _ _ O
one _ _ O
run _ _ O
. _ _ O

# id 627ac041-2ca0-47c1-bb08-c47c454fc8f1	domain=train
in _ _ O
2010 _ _ O
, _ _ O
sony _ _ B-GRP
pictures _ _ I-GRP
television _ _ I-GRP
, _ _ O
the _ _ O
show _ _ O
's _ _ O
production _ _ O
company _ _ O
, _ _ O
released _ _ O
an _ _ O
adaptation _ _ O
for _ _ O
the _ _ O
iphone _ _ B-PROD
, _ _ O
ipod _ _ B-PROD
touch _ _ I-PROD
, _ _ O
and _ _ O
ipad _ _ B-PROD
. _ _ O

# id 3842bf39-0f4d-4e60-aae0-c56a91a8f140	domain=train
# _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
little _ _ I-CW
mermaid _ _ I-CW
ii: _ _ I-CW
return _ _ I-CW
to _ _ I-CW
the _ _ I-CW
sea _ _ I-CW
tara _ _ B-PER
strong _ _ I-PER
and _ _ O
jodi _ _ B-PER
benson _ _ I-PER
( _ _ O
from _ _ O
the _ _ B-CW
little _ _ I-CW
mermaid _ _ I-CW
ii: _ _ I-CW
return _ _ I-CW
to _ _ I-CW
the _ _ I-CW
sea _ _ I-CW
) _ _ O

# id 7863296d-4d36-4fcd-8225-5854f8d4f761	domain=train
starring _ _ O
bing _ _ B-PER
crosby _ _ I-PER
and _ _ O
dorothy _ _ B-PER
lamour _ _ I-PER
, _ _ O
it _ _ O
is _ _ O
a _ _ O
musical _ _ B-CW
film _ _ I-CW
directed _ _ O
by _ _ O
a. _ _ B-PER
edward _ _ I-PER
sutherland _ _ I-PER
. _ _ O
